[
			
	{
	  "questionkey": "What are the details of the QuietGrowth Invite Program",
	  "answerkey": "The QuietGrowth Invite Program allows you to lower your QuietGrowth fee by inviting your friends to become QuietGrowth clients Invite a friend and we will waive QuietGrowth fee on an additional portoflio value of 5000 each for you and your friend when she deposits money into her QuietGrowth account You can benefit from the Invite Program for every friend of yours who becomes a QuietGrowth client",
	  "question": "What are the details of the QuietGrowth’s Invite Program?",
			  "answer": "The QuietGrowth Invite Program allows you to lower your QuietGrowth fee by inviting your friends to become QuietGrowth clients. Invite a friend and we will waive QuietGrowth fee on an additional portoflio value of $5,000 each for you and your friend when she deposits money into her QuietGrowth account.\n\nYou can benefit from the Invite Program for every friend of yours who becomes a QuietGrowth client.",
			  "url": "faq/What-are-the-details-of-the-QuietGrowths-Invite-Program"
		  , "section": "Fees" },
		  {
	  "questionkey": "Do I have to manually pay the ETF provider the underlying fund fee",
	  "answerkey": "A QuietGrowth portfolio comprises of various ETFs and each of the ETFs has its own underlying fund fee No you do not have to manually pay an ETF provider the underlying fund fee The ETF provider will deduct its ETF management fee also called as expense ratio from the cash that is invested in that ETF Underlying fund fees are factored in the real-time values of each of the ETFs we invest in This fee is expensed by the provider of each ETF and does not flow through QuietGrowth Hence this fee is not included in the QuietGrowth fee QuietGrowth offers different risk portfolios We have calculated the underlying fund fee for an overall portfolio for your reference This calculation is also referred to as Average Weighted Expense Ratio of all the funds in a QuietGrowth portfolio Refer to our pricing page for more information regarding this",
	  "question": "Do I have to manually pay the ETF provider the underlying fund fee?",
			  "answer": "A QuietGrowth portfolio comprises of various ETFs, and each of the ETFs has its own underlying fund fee. No, you do not have to manually pay an ETF provider the underlying fund fee.\n\nThe ETF provider will deduct its ETF management fee (also called as expense ratio) from the cash that is invested in that ETF. Underlying fund fees are factored in the real-time values of each of the ETFs we invest in. This fee is expensed by the provider of each ETF, and does not flow through QuietGrowth. Hence, this fee is not included in the QuietGrowth fee.\n\nQuietGrowth offers different risk portfolios. We have calculated the underlying fund fee for an overall portfolio, for your reference. This calculation is also referred to as Average Weighted Expense Ratio of all the funds in a QuietGrowth portfolio. Refer to our pricing page for more information regarding this.",
			  "url": "faq/Do-I-have-to-manually-pay-the-ETF-provider-the-underlying-fund-fee"
		  , "section": "Fees" },
		  {
	  "questionkey": "Do you charge for the new Statement of Advice that is generated as per my changed Personal Circumstances",
	  "answerkey": "No We do not charge a fee for the generation of a new Statement of Advice for you",
	  "question": "Do you charge for the new Statement of Advice that is generated as per my changed Personal Circumstances?",
			  "answer": "No. We do not charge a fee for the generation of a new Statement of Advice for you.",
			  "url": "faq/Do-you-charge-for-the-new-Statement-of-Advice-that-is-generated-as-per-my-changed-Personal-Circumstances"
		  , "section": "Fees" },
		  {
	  "questionkey": "Does a client of QuietGrowth has to pay trading fees separately to the brokerage firm",
	  "answerkey": "No Trading fees are already included in the fees charged by QuietGrowth to its client",
	  "question": "Does a client of QuietGrowth has to pay trading fees separately to the brokerage firm?",
			  "answer": "No. Trading fees are already included in the fees charged by QuietGrowth to its client.",
			  "url": "faq/Does-a-client-of-QuietGrowth-has-to-pay-trading-fees-separately-to-the-brokerage-firm"
		  , "section": "Fees" },
		  {
	  "questionkey": "Does a client of QuietGrowth has to pay custodial fees separately",
	  "answerkey": "No Custodial fees are already included in the fees charged by QuietGrowth to its client",
	  "question": "Does a client of QuietGrowth has to pay custodial fees separately?",
			  "answer": "No. Custodial fees are already included in the fees charged by QuietGrowth to its client.",
			  "url": "faq/Does-a-client-of-QuietGrowth-has-to-pay-custodial-fees-separately"
		  , "section": "Fees" },
		  {
	  "questionkey": "Does a client of QuietGrowth has to pay fees separately to the HLK Group",
	  "answerkey": "No The service rendered by the HLK Group to QuietGrowth is already included in the fees charged by QuietGrowth to its client For your information, HLK Group Pty Ltd acts as the MDA Provider Please refer to the Financial Services Guide for more information",
	  "question": "Does a client of QuietGrowth has to pay fees separately to the HLK Group?",
			  "answer": "No. The service rendered by the HLK Group to QuietGrowth is already included in the fees charged by QuietGrowth to its client.\n\nFor your information, HLK Group Pty Ltd acts as the MDA Provider. Please refer to the Financial Services Guide for more information.",
			  "url": "faq/Does-a-client-of-QuietGrowth-has-to-pay-fees-separately-to-the-HLK-Group"
		  , "section": "Fees" },
		  {
	  "questionkey": "Will I be charged exit fees due if I close my QuietGrowth account",
	  "answerkey": "You will not be charged with any exit fees if you close your QuietGrowth account",
	  "question": "Will I be charged exit fees due if I close my QuietGrowth account?",
			  "answer": "You will not be charged with any exit fees if you close your QuietGrowth account.",
			  "url": "faq/Will-I-be-charged-exit-fees-due-if-I-close-my-QuietGrowth-account"
		  , "section": "Fees" },
		  {
	  "questionkey": "Do you receive any compensation from ETF issuers for selecting their ETFs in your portfolios",
	  "answerkey": "No We do not receive any compensation from any of the ETF issuers Our service is aligned with the best interests of our clients",
	  "question": "Do you receive any compensation from ETF issuers for selecting their ETFs in your portfolios?",
			  "answer": "No. We do not receive any compensation from any of the ETF issuers. Our service is aligned with the best interests of our clients.",
			  "url": "faq/Do-you-receive-any-compensation-from-ETF-issuers-for-selecting-their-ETFs-in-your-portfolios"
		  , "section": "Fees" },
		  {
	  "questionkey": "Why do you have ETFs only apart from a nominal amount of cash and no other financial instruments in your portfolios",
	  "answerkey": "QuietGrowth believes in constructing its portoflios in the best interests of its clients We believe that exchange-traded funds ETFs are the best option to get exposure to various asset classes as long as suitable ETFs are available An ETF is an investment fund that is traded on stock exchanges much like stocks An ETF holds assets such as stocks bonds or commodities Most ETFs track an index such as the ASX 300 QuietGrowth uses ETFs that are traded in Australian Securities Exchange ASX and track an index QuietGrowth is not restricting itself to use ETFs only After all ETFs are a relatively recent innovation with a history dating from early 1990s only Whenever QuietGrowth finds out a better financial instrument to design its portfolios it will adopt the same",
	  "question": "Why do you have ETFs only (apart from a nominal amount of cash) and no other financial instruments in your portfolios?",
			  "answer": "QuietGrowth believes in constructing its portoflios in the best interests of its clients. We believe that exchange-traded funds (ETFs) are the best option to get exposure to various asset classes, as long as suitable ETFs are available.\n\nAn ETF is an investment fund that is traded on stock exchanges, much like stocks. An ETF holds assets such as stocks, bonds, or commodities. Most ETFs track an index, such as the ASX 300. QuietGrowth uses ETFs that are traded in Australian Securities Exchange (ASX) and track an index.\n\nQuietGrowth is not restricting itself to use ETFs only. After all, ETFs are a relatively recent innovation, with a history dating from early-1990s only. Whenever QuietGrowth finds out a better financial instrument to design its portfolios, it will adopt the same.",
			  "url": "faq/Why-do-you-have-ETFs-only-apart-from-a-nominal-amount-of-cash-and-no-other-financial-instruments-in-your-portfolios",
		  "section": "General questions"
	   },
		  {
	  "questionkey": "Why don't you display one 1 year and three 3 year portfolio returns in addition to ten 10 year returns",
	  "answerkey": "The investment methodology of QuietGrowth Portfolios is long-term oriented This is the reason for us to display a 10 year historical return chart in the website and to not calculate explicitly the one 1 year or three 3 year historical returns This is part of our attempt to communicate to the clients that they should consider their investing in QuietGrowth portfolios with a long-term perspective That said if you are inclined to know the one 1 year or three 3 year returns of QuietGrowth Portfolios you can calculate that by picking the required data for the specific time-period from the 10-year historical performance chart in the QuietGrowth website",
	  "question": "Why don't you display 1-year and 3-year portfolio returns, in addition to 10-year returns?",
			  "answer": "The investment methodology of QuietGrowth Portfolios is long-term oriented. This is the reason for us to display a 10-year historical return chart in the website, and to not calculate explicitly the 1-year or 3-year historical returns. This is part of our attempt to communicate to the clients that they should consider their investing in QuietGrowth portfolios with a long-term perspective.\n\nThat said, if you are inclined to know the 1-year or 3-year returns of QuietGrowth Portfolios, you can calculate that by picking the required data for the specific time-period from the 10-year historical performance chart in the QuietGrowth website.",
			  "url": "faq/Why-dont-you-display-1-year-and-3-year-portfolio-returns-in-addition-to-10-year-returns"
		  , "section": "General questions" },
		  {
	  "questionkey": "What will happen investments QuietGrowth acquired by another firm or ceases to conduct business",
	  "answerkey": "You need not worry because your brokerage account with our brokerage partner is held in your own name If any other firm acquires QuietGrowth and that firm decides to continue providing the service to you then there will not be any disruption in the service to you Your brokerage account will remain active in your own name and you can deposit or withdraw money whenever you want Even in the unlikely event of QuietGrowth ceasing to conduct business or cease to provide the MDA service to you because of getting acquired or because of business failure your brokerage account will remain active in your own name. Your securities and cash will continue to be held by our brokerage partner Saxo Capital Markets until you transfer your brokerage account to a new broker of your choice or you choose to liquidate your brokerage account to withdraw all your money. During this period our brokerage partner instead of us will not be providing the MDA service to you That is for example our brokerage partner will not provide online investment advice nor design investment portfolios nor invest your money as per your Investment Program nor ensure that your portfolios are rebalanced For more information read the answers to the following questions Where is my money held Where are my securities held",
	  "question": "What will happen to my investments if QuietGrowth is acquired by another firm, or ceases to conduct business?",
			  "answer": "You need not worry because your brokerage account with our brokerage partner is held in your own name.\n\nIf any other firm acquires QuietGrowth and that firm decides to continue providing the service to you, then there will not be any disruption in the service to you. Your brokerage account will remain active in your own name, and you can deposit or withdraw money whenever you want.\n\nEven in the unlikely event of QuietGrowth ceasing to conduct business or cease to provide the MDA service to you, because of getting acquired or because of business failure, your brokerage account will remain active in your own name. Your securities and cash will continue to be held by our brokerage partner Saxo Capital Markets, until you transfer your brokerage account to a new broker of your choice, or you choose to liquidate your brokerage account to withdraw all your money. During this period, our brokerage partner, instead of us, will not be providing the MDA service to you. That is, for example, our brokerage partner will not provide online investment advice, nor design investment portfolios, nor invest your money as per your Investment Program, nor ensure that your portfolios are rebalanced.\n\nFor more information, read the answers to the following questions:\n\n•   Where is my money held?\n\n•   Where are my securities held?",
			  "url": "faq/What-will-happen-to-my-investments-if-QuietGrowth-is-acquired-by-another-firm-or-ceases-to-conduct-business"
		  , "section": "General questions" },
		  {
	  "questionkey": "money transferred before you invest money be used by you for your own purposes discreetly",
	  "answerkey": "The money that you transfer to invest in ETFs will be transferred directly from your bank account to your brokerage account Your money will not be transferred from your bank account to QuietGrowth nor is QuietGrowth an intermediary in the flow of money from your bank account to your brokerage account So it is not possible for us at QuietGrowth to use the money transferred by you to be invested in QuietGrowth portfolios for our own purposes discreetly.\n\nFor more information read the answers to the following questions Where is my money held   Where are my securities held What will happen to my investments if QuietGrowth is acquired by another firm or ceases to conduct business",
	  "question": "Can the money transferred to you by me, before you invest that money in ETFs, be used by you for your own purposes discreetly?",
			  "answer": "The money that you transfer to invest in ETFs will be transferred directly from your bank account to your brokerage account. Your money will not be transferred from your bank account to QuietGrowth, nor is QuietGrowth an intermediary in the flow of money from your bank account to your brokerage account.\n\nSo, it is not possible for us at QuietGrowth to use the money transferred by you to be invested in QuietGrowth portfolios, for our own purposes discreetly.\n\nFor more information, read the answers to the following questions:\n\n•   Where is my money held?\n\n•   Where are my securities held?\n\n•   What will happen to my investments if QuietGrowth is acquired by another firm, or ceases to conduct business?",
			  "url": "faq/Can-the-money-transferred-to-you-by-me-before-you-invest-that-money-in-ETFs-be-used-by-you-for-your-own-purposes-discreetly"
		  , "section": "General questions" },
		  {
	  "questionkey": "tax information or documents do you provide your clients during tax time each year",
	  "answerkey": "After the end of each Financial Year an independent auditing of our investment management activity for that financial year will be conducted. As soon as this exercise is completed the Annual Investor Statement AIS which has details of your account activities and the Independent Auditor Report will be available to you At that time we will inform you by email about the availability of the documents This is as per regulations When the documents are ready for a particular financial year you will be able to download the documents from QuietGrowth website Annual Investor Statement can be downloaded in PDF and CSV file formats. You can use the Annual Investor Statement to file your tax returns",
	  "question": "What sort of tax information or documents do you provide your clients during tax time each year?",
			  "answer": "After the end of each Financial Year, an independent auditing of our investment management activity for that financial year will be conducted. As soon as this exercise is completed, the Annual Investor Statement (AIS), which has details of your account activities, and the Independent Auditor’s Report will be available to you. At that time, we will inform you by email about the availability of the documents. This is as per regulations.\n\nWhen the documents are ready for a particular financial year, you will be able to download the documents from QuietGrowth website. Annual Investor Statement can be downloaded in PDF and CSV file formats. You can use the Annual Investor Statement to file your tax returns.",
			  "url": "faq/What-sort-of-tax-information-or-documents-do-you-provide-your-clients-during-tax-time-each-year"
		  , "section": "Taxes" },
		  {
	  "questionkey": "terms commonly describe service",
	  "answerkey": "Robo advice digital advice automated investment management digital investment management online investment adviser digital investment advisor digital financial advisor online discretionary investment manager online wealth manager online financial advisor digital-only roboadvisor digital-only roboadvisory are the terms that are commonly used to describe our service",
	  "question": "What are the terms that are used commonly to describe your service?",
			  "answer": "Robo advice, digital advice, automated investment management, digital investment management, online investment adviser, digital investment advisor, digital financial advisor, online discretionary investment manager, online wealth manager, online financial advisor, digital-only roboadvisor, digital-only roboadvisory are the terms that are commonly used to describe our service.",
			  "url": "faq/What-are-the-terms-that-are-used-commonly-to-describe-your-service"
		  , "section": "General questions" },
		  {
	  "questionkey": "design questionnaire to determine risk tolerance score",
	  "answerkey": "QuietGrowth determines both the objective risk tolerance and the subjective risk tolerance of the projective client For that we split the questionnaire to determine the objective and subjective risk tolerance of the prospective client Some questions in the questionnaire will be based on objective risk to determine the ability of the prospective client to take risk and the rest of the questions will be on subjective risk to determine her willingness to take risk We will also identify and factor in for any inconsistencies in the manner in which the client answers those questions meant to determine the subjective risk tolerance Our methodology to determine the risk tolerance of the client has various aspects such as Objective ability of the client to take risk based on her projected savings after expenses throughout her working years projected retirement income and projected retirement spending needs Subjective willingness of the client to take risk Consistency of responses given by the client to the questions used to determine her subjective risk tolerance We have designed our client risk tolerance determination methodology in such a manner that a minimum number of questions are sufficient to determine the risk tolerance of the client to a reasonable accuracy We ask objective questions to determine whether the client is in line towards her saving enough money to afford her likely spending needs for the rest of her life This also helps us in partly determining how much risk the client can take with her investments We also ask subjective risk questions to determine the level of risk a client is willing to take Understanding the attitude of the client towards risk is important because ultimately the client needs to be comfortable with the risk element of her investment plan Analysing the consistency of the answers given by the client for the subjective risk questions helps us to know whether the client actually understands the questions that we ask For example if the client is willing to take a significantly higher risk as per her answer to one subjective question and is willing to take a much lower risk as per her answer to another subjective question then she is inconsistent in her answers Due to this inconsistency we might assign a lower subjective risk tolerance score than she would have got otherwise We are mindful of the number of questions we ask and intend to ask as few questions as possible We believe that our well-thought list of questions is sufficient and highly effective in identifying accurately the risk tolerance score of a client  After the QuietGrowth account is created for the client and the client starts investing we will continue to gather more information about her so that the accuracy of our understanding of her risk tolerance improves progressively Please refer to our Investment Methodology for more information",
	  "question": "How did you design the questionnaire to determine my risk tolerance score?",
			  "answer": "QuietGrowth determines both the objective risk tolerance and the subjective risk tolerance of the projective client. For that, we split the questionnaire to determine the objective and subjective risk tolerance of the prospective client. Some questions in the questionnaire will be based on objective risk to determine the ability of the prospective client to take risk, and the rest of the questions will be on subjective risk to determine her willingness to take risk. We will also identify and factor in for any inconsistencies in the manner in which the client answers those questions meant to determine the subjective risk tolerance.\n\nOur methodology to determine the risk tolerance of the client has various aspects such as:\n\n•  Objective ability of the client to take risk based on her projected savings after expenses throughout her working years, projected retirement income, and projected retirement spending needs\n\n•  Subjective willingness of the client to take risk\n\n•  Consistency of responses given by the client to the questions used to determine her subjective risk tolerance\n\nWe have designed our client risk tolerance determination methodology in such a manner that a minimum number of questions are sufficient to determine the risk tolerance of the client to a reasonable accuracy.\n\nWe ask objective questions to determine whether the client is in line towards her saving enough money to afford her likely spending needs for the rest of her life. This also helps us in partly determining how much risk the client can take with her investments.\n\nWe also ask subjective risk questions to determine the level of risk a client is willing to take. Understanding the attitude of the client towards risk is important because ultimately the client needs to be comfortable with the risk element of her investment plan.\n\nAnalysing the consistency of the answers given by the client for the subjective risk questions helps us to know whether the client actually understands the questions that we ask. For example, if the client is willing to take a significantly higher risk as per her answer to one subjective question, and is willing to take a much lower risk as per her answer to another subjective question, then she is inconsistent in her answers. Due to this inconsistency, we might assign a lower subjective risk tolerance score than she would have got otherwise.\n\nWe are mindful of the number of questions we ask, and intend to ask as few questions as possible. We believe that our well-thought list of questions is sufficient and highly effective in identifying accurately the risk tolerance score of a client. After the QuietGrowth account is created for the client and the client starts investing, we will continue to gather more information about her so that the accuracy of our understanding of her risk tolerance improves progressively.\n\nPlease refer to our Investment Methodology for more information.",
			  "url": "faq/How-did-you-design-the-questionnaire-to-determine-my-risk-tolerance-score"
		  , "section": "Questionnaire to determine risk tolerance score" },
		  {
	  "questionkey": "new Statement of Advice Personal Circumstances change",
	  "answerkey": "Yes a new Statement of Advice will be issued to you when you modify your Personal Circumstances You can modify your Personal Circumstances at most once a month",
	  "question": "If my Personal Circumstances change, can I get a new Statement of Advice?",
			  "answer": "Yes, a new Statement of Advice will be issued to you when you modify your Personal Circumstances. You can modify your Personal Circumstances at most once a month.",
			  "url": "faq/If-my-Personal-Circumstances-change-can-I-get-a-new-Statement-of-Advice"
		  , "section": "Questionnaire to determine risk tolerance score" },
		  {
	  "questionkey": "factor outside investments existing ownership stocks and bonds when you create my QuietGrowth portfolio",
	  "answerkey": "QuietGrowth asks the client the total value of liquid assets and the total value of illiquid assets owned by the client as part of the questionnaire in order to determine the risk tolerance score of that client However as of now QuietGrowth does not seek specific details on what these assets comprise of and hence does not factor while creating the QuietGrowth portfolio for that client",
	  "question": "Do you factor in my outside investments, such as existing ownership of certain stocks and bonds, when you create my QuietGrowth portfolio?",
			  "answer": "QuietGrowth asks the client the total value of liquid assets and the total value of illiquid assets owned by the client as part of the questionnaire in order to determine the risk tolerance score of that client. However, as of now, QuietGrowth does not seek specific details on what these assets comprise of, and hence does not factor while creating the QuietGrowth portfolio for that client.",
			  "url": "faq/Do-you-factor-in-my-outside-investments-such-as-existing-ownership-of-certain-stocks-and-bonds-when-you-create-my-QuietGrowth-portfolio"
		  , "section": "Your Investment Plan" },
		  {
	  "questionkey": "Do you have an investment strategy or investment methodology",
	  "answerkey": "Yes we do have our investment methodology and we have articulated it in a dedicated webpage Please read it here",
	  "question": "Do you have an investment strategy or investment methodology?",
			  "answer": "Yes, we do have our investment methodology, and we have articulated it in a dedicated webpage. Please read it here.",
			  "url": "faq/Do-you-have-an-investment-strategy-or-investment-methodology"
		  , "section": "Your Investment Plan" },
		  {
	  "questionkey": "Why the target mix of asset classes in my portfolio is constant irrespective of how much I invest and the frequency I invest",
	  "answerkey": "For optimal risk-adjusted returns the determination of various asset classes and the computation of the most appropriate mix of those asset classes is important For your risk tolerance score an appropriate portfolio mix is designed However the amount you invest through QuietGrowth and the frequency at which you invest has no relation with your risk tolerance score So you will continue to be suggested with the same portfolio associated with your risk tolerance score Just to clarify more the amount of money that you have does affect your risk tolerance score Everything else remaining constant the more money you have the higher your risk tolerance should be and hence a different target mix of asset classes in your portoflio QuietGrowth factors this in by asking you how much liquid and illiquid assets you have along with other questions in order to determine your financial health These inputs will be used while calculating your risk tolerance score",
	  "question": "Why the target mix of asset classes in my portfolio is constant irrespective of how much I invest and the frequency I invest?",
			  "answer": "For optimal risk-adjusted returns, the determination of various asset classes and the computation of the most appropriate mix of those asset classes is important. For your risk tolerance score, an appropriate portfolio mix is designed. However, the amount you invest through QuietGrowth and the frequency at which you invest has no relation with your risk tolerance score. So, you will continue to be suggested with the same portfolio associated with your risk tolerance score.\n\nJust to clarify more, the amount of money that you have does affect your risk tolerance score. Everything else remaining constant, the more money you have, the higher your risk tolerance should be, and hence a different target mix of asset classes in your portoflio. QuietGrowth factors this in by asking you how much liquid and illiquid assets you have, along with other questions, in order to determine your financial health. These inputs will be used while calculating your risk tolerance score.",
			  "url": "faq/Why-the-target-mix-of-asset-classes-in-my-portfolio-is-constant-irrespective-of-how-much-I-invest-and-the-frequency-I-invest"
		  , "section": "Your Investment Plan" },
		  {
	  "questionkey": "Can I replace any of the ETF in the QuietGrowth Portfolios with own choices",
	  "answerkey": "No We have opted for some specific ETF in each of the QuietGrowth Portfolios that we offer because we believe that these ETF are the best choice to invest in each of the asset classes of the our portfolios",
	  "question": "Can I replace any of the ETFs in the QuietGrowth Portfolios with own choices?",
			  "answer": "No. We have opted for some specific ETFs in each of the QuietGrowth Portfolios that we offer because we believe that these ETFs are the best choice to invest in each of the asset classes of the our portfolios.",
			  "url": "faq/Can-I-replace-any-of-the-ETFs-in-the-QuietGrowth-Portfolios-with-own-choices"
		  , "section": "Your Investment Plan" },
		  {
	  "questionkey": "If my portfolio loses its value and falls below the minimum amount required to invest initially do I need to deposit more cash",
	  "answerkey": "No For the Individual and Joint account types  the minimum initial investment through a QuietGrowth portfolio is $2000 However  if your portfolio value falls below $2000 then you will not be required to deposit more cash to ensure that the portfolio value is at least $2000 For the SMSF and Trust account types the minimum initial investment through a QuietGrowth portfolio is $10000  However if your portfolio value falls below $10000 then you will not be required to deposit more cash to ensure that the portfolio value is at least $10000",
	  "question": "If my portfolio loses its value and falls below the minimum amount required to invest initially, do I need to deposit more cash?",
			  "answer": "No.\n\nFor the Individual and Joint account types, the minimum initial investment through a QuietGrowth portfolio is $2,000. However, if your portfolio value falls below $2,000, then you will not be required to deposit more cash to ensure that the portfolio value is at least $2,000.\n\nFor the SMSF and Trust account types, the minimum initial investment through a QuietGrowth portfolio is $10,000. However, if your portfolio value falls below $10,000, then you will not be required to deposit more cash to ensure that the portfolio value is at least $10,000.",
			  "url": "faq/If-my-portfolio-loses-its-value-and-falls-below-the-minimum-amount-required-to-invest-initially-do-I-need-to-deposit-more-cash"
		  , "section": "Your Investment Plan" },
		  {
	  "questionkey": "Do you invest my deposits all at once or you do dollar cost averaging",
	  "answerkey": "Whenever you deposit sufficient funds QuietGrowth will invest your funds all at once We do not do dollar cost averaging by timing the investing events over a period of time The asset classes in a QuietGrowth portfolio are multiple and relatively uncorrelated Hence if one or more asset classes are up at a certain point of time usually the other assets are likely to be down For this reason the investing practice of dollar cost averaging is not necessary for our portfolios",
	  "question": "Do you invest my deposits all at once, or you do dollar cost averaging?",
			  "answer": "Whenever you deposit sufficient funds, QuietGrowth will invest your funds all at once. We do not do dollar cost averaging by timing the investing events over a period of time.\n\nThe asset classes in a QuietGrowth portfolio are multiple and relatively uncorrelated. Hence, if one or more asset classes are up at a certain point of time, usually the other assets are likely to be down. For this reason, the investing practice of dollar cost averaging is not necessary for our portfolios.",
			  "url": "faq/Do-you-invest-my-deposits-all-at-once-or-you-do-dollar-cost-averaging"
		  , "section": "Your Investment Plan" },
		  {
	  "questionkey": "Will QuietGrowth hold my individual stocks or bonds in addition to the QuietGrowth Portfolio it suggests",
	  "answerkey": "No We do not allow our clients to use their brokerage account that we open exclusively for their QuietGrowth Portfolios to hold any of their outside securities such as individual stocks or bonds",
	  "question": "Will QuietGrowth hold my individual stocks or bonds in addition to the QuietGrowth Portfolio it suggests?",
			  "answer": "No. We do not allow our clients to use their brokerage account, that we open exclusively for their QuietGrowth Portfolios, to hold any of their outside securities such as individual stocks or bonds.",
			  "url": "faq/Will-QuietGrowth-hold-my-individual-stocks-or-bonds-in-addition-to-the-QuietGrowth-Portfolio-it-suggests"
		  , "section": "Your Investment Plan" },
		  {
	  "questionkey": "What is the time frame you refer to when you suggest to invest for the long-term",
			  "answerkey": "We have mentioned in our website that the investment through QuietGrowth is for the long-term To enjoy the benefits of diversification of QuietGrowth portfolios in an increasing manner you would need to stay invested for at least 10 years The probability of loss of your investment in a diversified portfolio decreases as you stay invested for more number of years So ideally your investment in QuietGrowth portfolios should not include your investments with a very short time horizon of few months or an year If you are thinking of a big ticket purchase such as a house within a year and you cannot afford to lose a part of your money till the purchasing event because of market volatility then you should not invest that amount in a QuietGrowth Portfolio Instead you should park that money in a term deposit till the purchasing event",
			  
	  "question": "What is the time frame you refer to when you suggest to invest for the long-term?",
			  "answer": "We have mentioned in our website that the investment through QuietGrowth is for the long-term. To enjoy the benefits of diversification of QuietGrowth portfolios in an increasing manner, you would need to stay invested for at least 10 years. The probability of loss of your investment in a diversified portfolio decreases as you stay invested for more number of years.\n\nSo, ideally, your investment in QuietGrowth portfolios should not include your investments with a very short time horizon of few months or an year. If you are thinking of a big ticket purchase, such as a house, within a year, and you cannot afford to lose a part of your money till the purchasing event because of market volatility, then you should not invest that amount in a QuietGrowth Portfolio. Instead you should park that money in a term deposit till the purchasing event.",
			  "url": "faq/What-is-the-time-frame-you-refer-to-when-you-suggest-to-invest-for-the-long-term"
		  , "section": "Your Investment Plan" },
		  {
	  "questionkey": "Do you rebalance a portfolio whose value is less than 10000",
	  "answerkey": "No we do not rebalance a portfolio whose value is less than $10000",
	  "question": "Do you rebalance a portfolio whose value is less than $10,000?",
			  "answer": "No, we do not rebalance a portfolio whose value is less than $10,000.",
			  "url": "faq/Do-you-rebalance-a-portfolio-whose-value-is-less-than-10000"
		  , "section": "Your Investment Plan" },
		  {
	  "questionkey": "Do you rebalance a portfolio that is not a fully-diversified portfolio",
	  "answerkey": "No We do not rebalance a portfolio that is not a fully-diversified portfolio To know about what we mean by a fully diversified portfolio please refer here",
	  "question": "Do you rebalance a portfolio that is not a fully-diversified portfolio?",
			  "answer": "No. We do not rebalance a portfolio that is not a fully-diversified portfolio.\n\nTo know about what we mean by a 'fully-diversified portfolio', please refer here.",
			  "url": "faq/Do-you-rebalance-a-portfolio-that-is-not-a-fully-diversified-portfolio"
		  , "section": "Your Investment Plan" },
		  {
	  "questionkey": "Can I choose what to do to with the dividends that get paid out What are my options with dividends",
	  "answerkey": "The default option is we reinvesting the dividend amount towards the purchase of ETF after sufficient cash is accumulated to execute a buy trade Instead if you choose to withdraw the dividend amount then you can let us know your preference so that we will stop reinvesting the dividends and thus enabling you to withdraw some cash Please note that you can withdraw cash only above the minimum withdrawal limit Requesting for withdrawal of dividends is not suggested by us unless you have a need for that cash",
	  "question": "Can I choose what to do to with the dividends that get paid out? What are my options with dividends?",
			  "answer": "The default option is we reinvesting the dividend amount towards the purchase of ETFs, after sufficient cash is accumulated to execute a buy trade.\n\nInstead, if you choose to withdraw the dividend amount, then you can let us know your preference so that we will stop reinvesting the dividends and thus enabling you to withdraw some cash. Please note that you can withdraw cash only above the minimum withdrawal limit. Requesting for withdrawal of dividends is not suggested by us, unless you have a need for that cash.",
			  "url": "faq/Can-I-choose-what-to-do-to-with-the-dividends-that-get-paid-out-What-are-my-options-with-dividends"
		  , "section": "Your Investment Plan" },
		  {
	  "questionkey": "Can I use a QuietGrowth portfolio as the core of my core satellite approach of investing",
	  "answerkey": "Yes If you adopt the core satellite investing approach then QuietGrowth portfolios can serve as the core The highly diversified low cost nature of QuietGrowth portfolios enables you to create the core of your investments with our risk-optimised portfolios Then depending on your or your traditional wealth managers preference various other investment options outside QuietGrowth portfolios can serve as satellite allocations Refer to our investment methodology for more information",
	  "question": "Can I use a QuietGrowth portfolio as the core of my core-satellite approach of investing?",
			  "answer": "Yes. If you adopt the core-satellite investing approach, then QuietGrowth portfolios can serve as the ‘core’.\n\nThe highly-diversified, low-cost nature of QuietGrowth portfolios enables you to create the core of your investments with our risk-optimised portfolios. Then, depending on your or your traditional wealth manager’s preference, various other investment options, outside QuietGrowth portfolios, can serve as 'satellite' allocations. Refer to our investment methodology for more information.",
			  "url": "faq/Can-I-use-a-QuietGrowth-portfolio-as-the-core-of-my-core-satellite-approach-of-investing"
		  , "section": "Your Investment Plan" },
		  {
	  "questionkey": "Can I do socially responsible investing through QuietGrowth",
	  "answerkey": "We are sorry As of now if you intend to do any specific socially responsible or ethical investing then you will not be able to do it through QuietGrowth We cheer ethical investing from the sidelines Please refer to our Ethical Investing knowledge resource for more information",
	  "question": "Can I do socially responsible investing through QuietGrowth?",
			  "answer": "We are sorry. As of now, if you intend to do any specific socially responsible or ethical investing, then you will not be able to do it through QuietGrowth.\n\nWe cheer ethical investing from the sidelines. Please refer to our 'Ethical Investing' knowledge resource for more information.",
			  "url": "faq/Can-I-do-socially-responsible-investing-through-QuietGrowth"
		  , "section": "Your Investment Plan" },
		  {
	  "questionkey": "Can I do thematic investing or sector-investing through QuietGrowth Portfolios",
			  "answerkey": "No the QuietGrowth Portfolios are not thematic portfolios Your portfolio will not get extensive exposure to a short-term macroeconomic theme or trend because it is very difficult to predict the outperformance of such a theme or trend QuietGrowth Portfolios are not sector-based portfolios Your portfolio will not get extensive exposure to a specific sector with an expectation of that sector outperforming the broad market indices in the short term This is because it is very difficult to predict the outperformance of a specific sector For your information, some of the prominent sectors we consider in our analysis are Consumer discretionary Consumer staples Energy Financials Health care Industrials Information technology Materials Real estate Telecommunications Utilities",
			  
	  "question": "Can I do thematic investing or sector-investing through QuietGrowth Portfolios?",
			  "answer": "No, the QuietGrowth Portfolios are not thematic portfolios. Your portfolio will not get extensive exposure to a short-term macroeconomic theme or trend, because it is very difficult to predict the outperformance of such a theme or trend.\n\nQuietGrowth Portfolios are not sector-based portfolios. Your portfolio will not get extensive exposure to a specific sector, with an expectation of that sector outperforming the broad market indices in the short term. This is because it is very difficult to predict the outperformance of a specific sector.\n\nFor your information, some of the prominent sectors we consider in our analysis are:\n\n•   Consumer discretionary\n\n•   Consumer staples\n\n•   Energy\n\n•   Financials\n\n•   Health care\n\n•   Industrials\n\n•   Information technology\n\n•   Materials\n\n•   Real estate\n\n•   Telecommunications\n\n•   Utilities",
			  "url": "faq/Can-I-do-thematic-investing-or-sector-investing-through-QuietGrowth-Portfolios"
		  , "section": "Your Investment Plan" },
		  {
	  "questionkey": "Do you include private equity funds in QuietGrowth Portfolios",
			  "answerkey": "No we do not include private equity funds in QuietGrowth Portfolios as of now Not all private equity funds are equal and it is not preferable to invest in a private equity fund just because that fund happens to be a private equity fund Like most of the other alternate investment opportunities it is prudent to stay away from most of private equity funds except for certain private equity funds that are best-in-class However it is difficult to participate in such high-quality private equity funds especially with favourable terms of participation so that the interests of QuietGrowth clients are catered to So whenever QuietGrowth gets an opportunity to participate with favourable terms in these high-quality private equity funds we will certainly consider",
			  
	  "question": "Do you include private equity funds in QuietGrowth Portfolios?",
			  "answer": "No, we do not include private equity funds in QuietGrowth Portfolios, as of now.\n\nNot all private equity funds are equal, and it is not preferable to invest in a private equity fund, just because that fund happens to be a private equity fund. Like most of the other alternate investment opportunities, it is prudent to stay away from most of private equity funds, except for certain private equity funds that are best-in-class. However, it is difficult to participate in such high-quality private equity funds, especially with favourable terms of participation so that the interests of QuietGrowth clients are catered to. So, whenever QuietGrowth gets an opportunity to participate with favourable terms in these high-quality private equity funds, we will certainly consider.",
			  "url": "faq/Do-you-include-private-equity-funds-in-QuietGrowth-Portfolios"
		  , "section": "Your Investment Plan" },
		  {
	  "questionkey": "Do you include cryptocurrencies in QuietGrowth Portfolios",
			  "answerkey": "No we do not include cryptocurrencies such as bitcoin in QuietGrowth Portfolios We recognise cryptocurrencies as an asset class However we have decided to exclude as of now this asset class in the construction of our portfolios For more information please refer to our opinion Investing aspects pertaining to cryptocurrencies",
			  
	  "question": "Do you include cryptocurrencies in QuietGrowth Portfolios?",
			  "answer": "No, we do not include cryptocurrencies such as bitcoin in QuietGrowth Portfolios.\n\nWe recognise cryptocurrencies as an asset class. However, we have decided to exclude, as of now, this asset class in the construction of our portfolios. For more information, please refer to our opinion 'Investing aspects pertaining to cryptocurrencies'.",
			  "url": "faq/Do-you-include-cryptocurrencies-in-QuietGrowth-Portfolios"
		  , "section": "Your Investment Plan" },
		  {
	  "questionkey": "Why do you use ETFs in your portfolio instead of individual stocks and bonds",
			  "answerkey": "We use ETFs in our portfolios because we believe ETFs have various advantages ETFs are a convenient way to diversify an asset class in a portfolio Opting for few ETFs in a portfolio is preferable to opting for few thousand individual stocks to achieve the same level of diversification of the portfolio This is in spite of the ETF management fees incurred for each of the ETF if we opt for ETFs Other costs include trading fees and bid-ask spreads Trading fees are lower if we opt for fewer ETFs instead of few thousand individual stocks Bid-ask spread can be low for ETFs that we prefer in our Portfolios whereas the bid-ask spread can be high for certain specific individual stocks with low liquidity (Please note that the trading fees is included in our QuietGrowth fee whereas the ETF management fees and bid-ask spreads are incurred by you Refer to our pricing page for more information.)\n\nSimilar is the case of opting for bond ETFs instead of individual bonds There are other advantages for opting for ETFs Whenever we modify the portfolio mix by altering the allocation of various asset classes it is easier to implement that modification when we use ETFs to represent these asset classes Sometimes ETFs can also be more tax efficient because of lesser realised capital gains tax incurred by the ETF issuer while managing that ETF compared to us trying to replicate that ETF ourselves by buying and selling a large number of individual stocks That said the innovation of direct indexing by automated investment management services has emerged in the U.S since 2015 We are positive about this Using this method QuietGrowth can opt for individual stocks instead of ETFs We at QuietGrowth will not be introducing this at least for sometime",
			  
	  "question": "Why do you use ETFs in your portfolio instead of individual stocks and bonds?",
			  "answer": "We use ETFs in our portfolios because we believe ETFs have various advantages. ETFs are a convenient way to diversify an asset class in a portfolio. Opting for few ETFs in a portfolio is preferable to opting for few thousand individual stocks to achieve the same level of diversification of the portfolio. This is in spite of the ETF management fees incurred for each of the ETF, if we opt for ETFs.\n\nOther costs include trading fees and bid-ask spreads. Trading fees are lower if we opt for fewer ETFs instead of few thousand individual stocks. Bid-ask spread can be low for ETFs that we prefer in our Portfolios, whereas the bid-ask spread can be high for certain specific individual stocks with low liquidity. (Please note that the trading fees is included in our QuietGrowth fee, whereas the ETF management fees and bid-ask spreads are incurred by you. Refer to our pricing page for more information.)\n\nSimilar is the case of opting for bond ETFs instead of individual bonds.\n\nThere are other advantages for opting for ETFs. Whenever we modify the portfolio mix by altering the allocation of various asset classes, it is easier to implement that modification when we use ETFs to represent these asset classes. Sometimes, ETFs can also be more tax efficient because of lesser realised capital gains tax incurred by the ETF issuer while managing that ETF, compared to us trying to replicate that ETF ourselves by buying and selling a large number of individual stocks.\n\nThat said, the innovation of direct indexing by automated investment management services has emerged in the U.S since 2015. We are positive about this. Using this method, QuietGrowth can opt for individual stocks instead of ETFs. We at QuietGrowth will not be introducing this at least for sometime.",
			  "url": "faq/Why-do-you-use-ETFs-in-your-portfolio-instead-of-individual-stocks-and-bonds"
		  , "section": "Your Investment Plan" },
		  {
	  "questionkey": "Can I modify my QuietGrowth portfolio as per my religious preferences",
	  "answerkey": "We are sorry but you will not be able to customise your QuietGrowth portfolio as per any of your preferences other than altering the risk tolerance score associated with your QuietGrowth portfolio",
	  "question": "Can I modify my QuietGrowth portfolio as per my religious preferences?",
			  "answer": "We are sorry, but you will not be able to customise your QuietGrowth portfolio as per any of your preferences other than altering the risk tolerance score associated with your QuietGrowth portfolio.",
			  "url": "faq/Can-I-modify-my-QuietGrowth-portfolio-as-per-my-religious-preferences"
		  , "section": "Your Investment Plan" },
		  {
	  "questionkey": "How do you calculate the historical performance of QuietGrowth Portfolios",
	  "answerkey": "Some of the practices we follow to calculate the historical performance of QuietGrowth Portfolios can be found in this webpage",
	  "question": "How do you calculate the historical performance of QuietGrowth Portfolios?",
			  "answer": "Some of the practices we follow to calculate the historical performance of QuietGrowth Portfolios can be found in this webpage.",
			  "url": "faq/How-do-you-calculate-the-historical-performance-of-QuietGrowth-Portfolios"
		  , "section": "Your Investment Plan" },
		  {
	  "questionkey": "Why QuietGrowth does not have its own Product Disclosure Statement PDS",
	  "answerkey": "QuietGrowth enters into a contract with the client to provide a Managed Discretionary Account MDA service to the client QuietGrowth has prepared a Financial Services Guide FSG pertaining to this MDA service as per regulations The FSG is required to contain information about fees and costs in relation to the MDA service as if the FSG were a Product Disclosure Statement PDS for such a managed investment product So in short QuietGrowth does not have to prepare a Product Disclosure Statement PDS",
	  "question": "Why QuietGrowth does not have its own Product Disclosure Statement (PDS)?",
			  "answer": "QuietGrowth enters into a contract with the client to provide a Managed Discretionary Account (MDA) service to the client. QuietGrowth has prepared a Financial Services Guide (FSG) pertaining to this MDA service, as per regulations. The FSG is required to contain information about fees and costs in relation to the MDA service, as if the FSG were a Product Disclosure Statement (PDS) for such a managed investment product. So, in short, QuietGrowth does not have to prepare a Product Disclosure Statement (PDS).",
			  "url": "faq/Why-QuietGrowth-does-not-have-its-own-Product-Disclosure-Statement-PDS"
		  , "section": "Structure of QuietGrowth service" },
		  {
	  "questionkey": "What is the minimum amount required to be deposited initially in a QuietGrowth portfolio",
	  "answerkey": "For the Individual and Joint account types the minimum initial investment in a QuietGrowth portfolio is $2000 For the SMSF and Trust account types the minimum initial investment in the first QuietGrowth portfolio is $10000 For the SMSF and Trust account types the minimum initial investment in the second or subsequent QuietGrowth portfolios is $2000",
	  "question": "What is the minimum amount required to be deposited initially in a QuietGrowth portfolio?",
			  "answer": "For the Individual and Joint account types, the minimum initial investment in a QuietGrowth portfolio is $2,000.\n\nFor the SMSF and Trust account types, the minimum initial investment in the first QuietGrowth portfolio is $10,000. For the SMSF and Trust account types, the minimum initial investment in the second or subsequent QuietGrowth portfolios is $2,000.",
			  "url": "faq/What-is-the-minimum-amount-required-to-be-deposited-initially-in-a-QuietGrowth-portfolio"
		  , "section": "Your account" },
		  {
	  "questionkey": "When will my first portfolio have exposure to all the asset classes mentioned in my investment plan",
	  "answerkey": "As long as your total funds deposited for investing in your first portfolio are less than $10000 QuietGrowth phases-in your funds towards purchase of one ETF after the other That is till the time your total deposits are less than $10000 you will have a partly-diversified portfolio only As you deposit progressively towards $10000 we will buy more ETFs progressively towards your fully-diversified first portfolio As soon as your total deposits reach $10,000 you will have exposure to the fully-diversified QuietGrowth portfolio So it is preferable if you could invest more towards reaching $10000 in deposits in your first portfolio If your total deposits are less than $10000 then the performance of your portfolio will be very different than the performance of the QuietGrowth model portfolio of the same risk score because we might have not purchased all the ETFs in your portfolio",
	  "question": "When will my first portfolio have exposure to all the asset classes mentioned in my investment plan?",
	  "answer": "As long as your total funds deposited for investing in your first portfolio are less than $10,000, QuietGrowth phases-in your funds towards purchase of one ETF after the other.\n\nThat is, till the time your total deposits are less than $10,000, you will have a partly-diversified portfolio only. As you deposit progressively towards $10,000, we will buy more ETFs progressively towards your fully-diversified first portfolio. As soon as your total deposits reach $10,000, you will have exposure to the fully-diversified QuietGrowth portfolio. So, it is preferable if you could invest more towards reaching $10,000 in deposits in your first portfolio.\n\nIf your total deposits are less than $10,000, then the performance of your portfolio will be very different than the performance of the QuietGrowth model portfolio of the same risk score because we might have not purchased all the ETFs in your portfolio.\n\nTo know about what we mean by a 'fully-diversified portfolio', please refer here.",
	  "url": "faq/When-will-my-first-portfolio-have-exposure-to-all-the-asset-classes-mentioned-in-my-investment-plan"
	  , "section": "Your account" },
		  {
	  "questionkey": "Is there a need for me to login to my brokerage account that you would create when my QuietGrowth account is created",
	  "answerkey": "There is no need for you to log in to your Saxo brokerage account because you can view the details of your portfolios in the QuietGrowth website itself That said you may login to your brokerage account at any point of time Please note that the website of the brokerage account provider is not maintained by QuietGrowth",
	  "question": "Is there a need for me to login to my brokerage account that you would create when my QuietGrowth account is created?",
			  "answer": "There is no need for you to log in to your Saxo brokerage account, because you can view the details of your portfolios in the QuietGrowth website itself. That said, you may login to your brokerage account at any point of time.\n\nPlease note that the website of the brokerage account provider is not maintained by QuietGrowth.",
			  "url": "faq/Is-there-a-need-for-me-to-login-to-my-brokerage-account-that-you-would-create-when-my-QuietGrowth-account-is-created"
		  , "section": "Your account" },
		  {
	  "questionkey": "Is there a need for me to contact directly the support team at the brokerage firm during or after my brokerage account creation process",
			  "answerkey": "There is no need for you to contact directly the support team at the brokerage firm Saxo during or after your brokerage account creation process We at QuietGrowth will be happy to be the single point of contact for you so that you can avoid the hassle of contacting the support team at the brokerage firm You can email us with any query related to your brokerage account and we will contact the brokerage firm internally to attempt to resolve the issue you are facing",
			  
	  "question": "Is there a need for me to contact directly the support team at the brokerage firm, during or after my brokerage account creation process?",
			  "answer": "There is no need for you to contact directly the support team at the brokerage firm, Saxo, during or after your brokerage account creation process. We at QuietGrowth will be happy to be the single point of contact for you, so that you can avoid the hassle of contacting the support team at the brokerage firm.\n\nYou can email us with any query related to your brokerage account, and we will contact the brokerage firm internally to attempt to resolve the issue you are facing.",
			  "url": "faq/Is-there-a-need-for-me-to-contact-directly-the-support-team-at-the-brokerage-firm-during-or-after-my-brokerage-account-creation-process"
		  , "section": "Your account" },
		  {
	  "questionkey": "Who should I contact if I have any account related question problem or suggestion",
	  "answerkey": "Please contact us by email accounts@quietgrowth.com.au with any account-related question problem or suggestion The preferred communication is through emails because a good proportion of queries would involve inputs from our team of experts We will call you back instead of emailing you back if there is a specific need",
	  "question": "Who should I contact if I have any account-related question, problem or suggestion?",
			  "answer": "Please contact us by email (accounts@quietgrowth.com.au) with any account-related question, problem or suggestion. The preferred communication is through emails, because a good proportion of queries would involve inputs from our team of experts. We will call you back instead of emailing you back, if there is a specific need.",
			  "url": "faq/Who-should-I-contact-if-I-have-any-account-related-question-problem-or-suggestion"
		  , "section": "Your account" },
		  {
	  "questionkey": "Can I execute the buy and sell trades myself for the money I deposit in QuietGrowth portfolios",
	  "answerkey": "No you cannot execute the buy and sell trades yourself for the money you deposit in QuietGrowth portfolios You delegate to QuietGrowth the task of managing the money that you deposit We provide you the QuietGrowth service through the Managed Discretionary Account MDA structure",
	  "question": "Can I execute the buy and sell trades myself for the money I deposit in QuietGrowth portfolios?",
			  "answer": "No, you cannot execute the buy and sell trades yourself for the money you deposit in QuietGrowth portfolios. You delegate to QuietGrowth the task of managing the money that you deposit. We provide you the QuietGrowth service through the Managed Discretionary Account (MDA) structure.",
			  "url": "faq/Can-I-execute-the-buy-and-sell-trades-myself-for-the-money-I-deposit-in-QuietGrowth-portfolios"
		  , "section": "Your account" },
		  {
	  "questionkey": "Why am I not able to execute buy or sell trades myself after I login to my brokerage account",
	  "answerkey": "You cannot execute the buy and sell trades yourself for the money you deposit in QuietGrowth portfolios You delegate to QuietGrowth the task of managing the money that you deposit We provide you the QuietGrowth service through the Managed Discretionary Account MDA structure The Saxo brokerage account provided to you is a read only account There is no need for you to log in to your Saxo brokerage account because you can view the details of your portfolios in the QuietGrowth website itself That said you may login to your brokerage account at any point of time Please note that the website of the brokerage account provider is not maintained by QuietGrowth",
	  "question": "Why am I not able to execute buy or sell trades myself after I login to my brokerage account?",
			  "answer": "You cannot execute the buy and sell trades yourself for the money you deposit in QuietGrowth portfolios. You delegate to QuietGrowth the task of managing the money that you deposit. We provide you the QuietGrowth service through the Managed Discretionary Account (MDA) structure.\n\nThe Saxo brokerage account provided to you is a read-only account. There is no need for you to log in to your Saxo brokerage account, because you can view the details of your portfolios in the QuietGrowth website itself. That said, you may login to your brokerage account at any point of time. Please note that the website of the brokerage account provider is not maintained by QuietGrowth.",
			  "url": "faq/Why-am-I-not-able-to-execute-buy-or-sell-trades-myself-after-I-login-to-my-brokerage-account"
		  , "section": "Your account" },
		  {
	  "questionkey": "Can I change the account type of my QuietGrowth account from individual to joint, or from joint to individual",
	  "answerkey": "Yes during the account creation process before the creation of the brokerage account associated with your QuietGrowth account you can change the account type of your QuietGrowth account from individual to joint or from joint to individual After the creation of the brokerage account associated with your QuietGrowth account during the account creation process you cannot change the account type of your QuietGrowth account from individual to joint or from joint to individual In such a scenario if you have an individual account and want to have a joint account you would need to create a new joint account with us Or if you have a joint account and want to have an individual account you would need to create a new individual account with us",
	  "question": "Can I change the account type of my QuietGrowth account from individual to joint, or from joint to individual?",
			  "answer": "Yes, during the account creation process before the creation of the brokerage account associated with your QuietGrowth account, you can change the account type of your QuietGrowth account — from individual to joint, or from joint to individual.\n\nAfter the creation of the brokerage account associated with your QuietGrowth account during the account creation process, you cannot change the account type of your QuietGrowth account — from individual to joint, or from joint to individual. In such a scenario, if you have an individual account and want to have a joint account, you would need to create a new joint account with us. Or, if you have a joint account and want to have an individual account, you would need to create a new individual account with us.",
			  "url": "faq/Can-I-change-the-account-type-of-my-QuietGrowth-account-from-individual-to-joint-or-from-joint-to-individual"
		  , "section": "Your account" },
		  {
	  "questionkey": "My current residential address has changed How can I change the address in my account details",
	  "answerkey": "Please inform us the new residential address Also please provide us with a proof of address in the form of a bank statement or a utility bill dated no longer than 3 months from today date which contains the name and the new address Please note that the name should match the name in the QuietGrowth records Then we will update the current residential address in QuietGrowth records and also internally communicate with the brokerage firm to update the records of your brokerage account",
	  "question": "My current residential address has changed. How can I change the address in my account details?",
			  "answer": "Please inform us the new residential address. Also, please provide us with a proof of address, in the form of a bank statement or a utility bill, dated no longer than 3 months from today's date, which contains the name and the new address. Please note that the name should match the name in the QuietGrowth records.\n\nThen, we will update the current residential address in QuietGrowth records, and also internally communicate with the brokerage firm to update the records of your brokerage account.",
			  "url": "faq/My-current-residential-address-has-changed-How-can-I-change-the-address-in-my-account-details"
		  , "section": "Your account" },
		  {
	  "questionkey": "I have now become a resident of a country other than Australia Should I inform you",
	  "answerkey": "As long as you are a QuietGrowth client you are required to keep us updated about your country of residency As a QuietGrowth client if you have now become a resident of another country other than Australia then your current residential address would have changed You are required to inform us",
	  "question": "I have now become a resident of a country other than Australia. Should I inform you?",
			  "answer": "As long as you are a QuietGrowth client, you are required to keep us updated about your country of residency.\n\nAs a QuietGrowth client, if you have now become a resident of another country other than Australia, then your current residential address would have changed. You are required to inform us.",
			  "url": "faq/I-have-now-become-a-resident-of-a-country-other-than-Australia-Should-I-inform-you"
		  , "section": "Your account" },
		  {
	  "questionkey": "If I pass away what happens to my individual account at QuietGrowth",
	  "answerkey": "If a client passes away then we will need the following documentation before we can take any instructions from a third party Death Certificate of the client Will and Grant of Probate OR Letters of Administration Proof of identity which can be a copy of the passport or government issued ID card from the administrator After these documents are submitted by the administrator and are approved by us we will take instructions from the administrator",
	  "question": "If I pass away, what happens to my individual account at QuietGrowth?",
			  "answer": "If a client passes away, then we will need the following documentation before we can take any instructions from a third party:\n\n1.   Death Certificate of the client.\n\n2.   Will and Grant of Probate, OR Letters of Administration.\n\n3.   Proof of identity, which can be a copy of the passport or government issued ID card, from the administrator.\n\nAfter these documents are submitted by the administrator and are approved by us, we will take instructions from the administrator.",
			  "url": "faq/If-I-pass-away-what-happens-to-my-individual-account-at-QuietGrowth"
		  , "section": "Your account" },
		  {
	  "questionkey": "When do you ask for a certified copy of my identification document",
	  "answerkey": "We ask for a certified copy of your identification document only when your online ID verification fails at the time of account creation For details on the nature of the identity document that we request please refer our Certifying the Identification Document webpage",
	  "question": "When do you ask for a certified copy of my identification document?",
			  "answer": "We ask for a certified copy of your identification document only when your online ID verification fails at the time of account creation.\n\nFor details on the nature of the identity document that we request, please refer our Certifying the Identification Document webpage.",
			  "url": "faq/When-do-you-ask-for-a-certified-copy-of-my-identification-document"
		  , "section": "Creating an account" },
		  {
	  "questionkey": "You requested a certified copy of my identification document  Can I send you my 100 point check document instead",
	  "answerkey": "We do not accept a 100 point check document For details on the nature of the identity document that we request please refer our Certifying the Identification Document webpage",
	  "question": "You requested a certified copy of my identification document. Can I send you my 100 point check document instead?",
			  "answer": "We do not accept a 100 point check document. For details on the nature of the identity document that we request, please refer our Certifying the Identification Document webpage.",
			  "url": "faq/You-requested-a-certified-copy-of-my-identification-document-Can-I-send-you-my-100-point-check-document-instead"
		  , "section": "Creating an account" },
		  {
	  "questionkey": "Why is a brokerage account created when my QuietGrowth account is created",
	  "answerkey": "When we create a QuietGrowth account for you a brokerage account in your name is also created This is because your securities and your cash are held in this brokerage account We need an execution and clearing broker to execute the buy and sell trades of your securities in QuietGrowth portfolios We provide you the QuietGrowth service through the Managed Discretionary Account MDA structure For more information refer MDA Structure For more information read the answers to the following questions Where are my securities held Where is my money held What are the advantages of Managed Discretionary Account MDA structure through which you offer your service",
	  "question": "Why is a brokerage account created when my QuietGrowth account is created?",
			  "answer": "When we create a QuietGrowth account for you, a brokerage account in your name is also created. This is because your securities and your cash are held in this brokerage account. We need an execution and clearing broker to execute the buy and sell trades of your securities in QuietGrowth portfolios.\n\nWe provide you the QuietGrowth service through the Managed Discretionary Account (MDA) structure. For more information, refer: MDA Structure\n\nFor more information, read the answers to the following questions:\n\n•   Where are my securities held?\n\n•   Where is my money held?\n\n•   What are the advantages of Managed Discretionary Account (MDA) structure through which you offer your service?",
			  "url": "faq/Why-is-a-brokerage-account-created-when-my-QuietGrowth-account-is-created"
		  , "section": "Creating an account" },
		  {
	  "questionkey": "Apart from the W-8BEN or W 8BEN E form do I need to consider anything else regarding US taxation rules",
			  "answerkey": "For the ETF in your QuietGrowth Portfolio that are domiciled in the US you might be subjected to the US Estate Taxes That is the deceased US non-resident who was not a US citizen might be subjected to US estate taxation with respect to her US-situated assets However these US Estate Taxes are applicable only if the US situated assets exceed certain limit Estate tax treaties between the US and other countries often provide more favorable tax treatment to nonresidents by limiting the type of asset considered situated in the US and subject to US estate taxation Executors for nonresident estates should consult such treaties where applicable US has an Estate Tax Treaty with Australia and that is a good news for you if you are an Australian resident QuietGrowth does not collect any form from you regarding the US Estate Taxes Please note that QuietGrowth does not provide any advice on tax related services The Internal Revenue Service IRS is a US government agency responsible for tax collection and tax law enforcement If you have queries about US Estate Taxes you would need to refer to the relevant instructions available in the IRS website or obtain advice from your tax expert",
			  
	  "question": "Apart from the W-8BEN or W-8BEN-E form, do I need to consider anything else regarding US taxation rules?",
			  "answer": "For the ETFs in your QuietGrowth Portfolio that are domiciled in the US, you might be subjected to the US Estate Taxes. That is, the deceased US non-resident who was not a US citizen might be subjected to US estate taxation with respect to her US-situated assets. However, these US Estate Taxes are applicable only if the US-situated assets exceed certain limit.\n\nEstate tax treaties between the U.S. and other countries often provide more favorable tax treatment to nonresidents by limiting the type of asset considered situated in the U.S. and subject to U.S. estate taxation. Executors for nonresident estates should consult such treaties where applicable. US has an Estate Tax Treaty with Australia and that is a good news for you, if you are an Australian resident.\n\nQuietGrowth does not collect any form from you regarding the US Estate Taxes.\n\nPlease note that QuietGrowth does not provide any advice on tax related services. The Internal Revenue Service (IRS) is a US government agency responsible for tax collection and tax law enforcement. If you have queries about US Estate Taxes, you would need to refer to the relevant instructions available in the IRS website, or obtain advice from your tax expert.",
			  "url": "faq/Apart-from-the-W-8BEN-or-W-8BEN-E-form-do-I-need-to-consider-anything-else-regarding-US-taxation-rules"
		  , "section": "Creating an account" },
		  {
	  "questionkey": "I am not a citizen nor a resident of Australia I live outside of Australia. Can I open an account",
	  "answerkey": "Yes you can open an account with QuietGrowth even if you are not a citizen nor a resident of Australia We accept international clients Restrictions for certain countries If you are a resident of certain specific countries, you would not be able to open an account with us The list of these specific countries that are not allowed keeps changing because of changing regulations and compliance policies So if you are not a citizen nor a resident of Australia you may start the onboarding process of creating a QuietGrowth account A good number of QuietGrowth clients are not residents of Australia Based on the residency and other details that are provided by you during the onboarding process our compliance team will decide whether we can create your QuietGrowth account or not Please note that if you are a US resident you will not be able to open an account For more details please refer to our answer to the question Can US residents open an account with QuietGrowth Why Australia Australia is a developed country with a robust rule of law healthy regulatory practices and a stable society So many people who live in countries facing significant uncertainties such as a risk of war internal strife social unrest low quality of governance high political risk financial instability and volatile currency favour transferring a part of their wealth to preferred destinations such as Australia Please refer to our transfer a part of your wealth to Australia knowledge resource for more information Tax implications Please be aware that you might need to file your annual tax returns in Australia as your brokerage account will be domiciled in Australia You can contact your tax consultant for more pertinent details as applicable in your case regarding investing through a brokerage account domiciled in Australia.",
			  
	  "question": "I am not a citizen nor a resident of Australia. I live outside of Australia. Can I open an account?",
	  "answer": "Yes, you can open an account with QuietGrowth even if you are not a citizen nor a resident of Australia. We accept international clients.\n\nRestrictions for certain countries\n\nIf you are a resident of certain specific countries, you would not be able to open an account with us. The list of these specific countries that are not allowed keeps changing because of changing regulations and compliance policies.\n\nSo, if you are not a citizen nor a resident of Australia, you may start the onboarding process of creating a QuietGrowth account. A good number of QuietGrowth clients are not residents of Australia. Based on the residency and other details that are provided by you during the onboarding process, our compliance team will decide whether we can create your QuietGrowth account or not.\n\nPlease note that if you are a US resident, you will not be able to open an account. For more details, please refer to our answer to the question: Can US residents open an account with QuietGrowth?\n\nWhy Australia\n\nAustralia is a developed country with a robust rule-of-law, healthy regulatory practices and a stable society. So, many people who live in countries facing significant uncertainties (such as a risk of war, internal strife, social unrest, low quality of governance, high political risk, financial instability and volatile currency) favour transferring a part of their wealth to preferred destinations such as Australia. Please refer to our 'transfer a part of your wealth to Australia' knowledge resource for more information.\n\nTax implications\n\nPlease be aware that you might need to file your annual tax returns in Australia, as your brokerage account will be domiciled in Australia. You can contact your tax consultant for more pertinent details, as applicable in your case, regarding investing through a brokerage account domiciled in Australia.",
	  "url": "faq/I-am-not-a-citizen-nor-a-resident-of-Australia-I-live-outside-of-Australia-Can-I-open-an-account"
		  , "section": "Creating an account — Residents of other countries" },
		  {
	  "questionkey": "Can a US citizen who is not a US resident open an account with QuietGrowth",
	  "answerkey": "Yes a US citizen who is not a US resident can open an account with QuietGrowth At the time of account creation we take a confirmation from anyone who is a US citizen that she is not a US non resident and she has been staying outside the US for more than six months",
	  "question": "Can a US citizen who is not a US resident open an account with QuietGrowth?",
			  "answer": "Yes, a US citizen who is not a US resident can open an account with QuietGrowth. At the time of account creation, we take a confirmation from anyone who is a US citizen that she is not a US non resident and she has been staying outside the US for more than six months.",
			  "url": "faq/Can-a-US-citizen-who-is-not-a-US-resident-open-an-account-with-QuietGrowth"
		  , "section": "Creating an account — Residents of other countries" },
		  {
	  "questionkey": "I am a US citizen who is not a US resident Is it required of me to submit the W 9 form",
	  "answerkey": "Yes if you are a US citizen who is not a US resident it is required of you to submit the W 9 form to us You would be sending us the W 9 form instead of W BEN or W 8BEN E form We suggest you to provide this form to us at the time of account creation or at a later date the sooner the better You can email us this form even after the creation of your account The Foreign Account Tax Compliance Act FATCA is a legislation of the United States targeting non compliance by US taxpayers with foreign accounts Under FATCA rules as of 1st July 2014 our brokerage partner must obtain self certification from Individual and Joint account holders to determine their non US or US status for tax purposes Then client accounts deemed reportable that is identified as US citizen or resident of US for tax purposes are then reported by our brokerage partner to the IRS via the Australian Tax Office ATO during the reporting periods",
	  "question": "I am a US citizen who is not a US resident. Is it required of me to submit the W-9 form?",
			  "answer": "Yes, if you are a US citizen who is not a US resident, it is required of you to submit the W-9 form to us. You would be sending us the W-9 form instead of W-BEN or W-8BEN-E form.\n\nWe suggest you to provide this form to us, at the time of account creation or at a later date — the sooner the better. You can email us this form, even after the creation of your account.\n\nThe Foreign Account Tax Compliance Act (FATCA) is a legislation of the United States targeting non-compliance by US taxpayers with foreign accounts. Under FATCA rules, as of 1st July 2014, our brokerage partner must obtain self-certification from Individual and Joint account holders to determine their non-US or US status for tax purposes. Then, client accounts deemed reportable (that is, identified as ‘US citizen’ or ‘resident of US’ for tax purposes) are then reported by our brokerage partner to the IRS via the Australian Tax Office (ATO) during the reporting periods.",
			  "url": "faq/I-am-a-US-citizen-who-is-not-a-US-resident-Is-it-required-of-me-to-submit-the-W-9-form"
		  , "section": "Creating an account — Residents of other countries" },
		  {
	  "questionkey": "Can a resident of any country open an account with QuietGrowth",
	  "answerkey": "All residents of Australia can open an account with QuietGrowth Residents of most countries other than Australia can open an account However residents of certain specific countries cannot open an account If you are a resident of a country other than Australia then go ahead to initiate your QuietGrowth account creation process After we collect your residency status details we will inform you whether a QuietGrowth account can be created for you or not The typical reason that residents of certain countries such as the US cannot open a QuietGrowth account is because of certain regulations in those countries In order for QuietGrowth to accept residents of those countries QuietGrowth needs to follow various extra rules stipulated by those countries which we does not intend to follow at this point of time",
	  "question": "Can a resident of any country open an account with QuietGrowth?",
			  "answer": "All residents of Australia can open an account with QuietGrowth. Residents of most countries, other than Australia, can open an account. However, residents of certain specific countries cannot open an account.\n\nIf you are a resident of a country other than Australia, then go ahead to initiate your QuietGrowth account creation process. After we collect your residency status details, we will inform you whether a QuietGrowth account can be created for you or not.\n\nThe typical reason that residents of certain countries, such as the US, cannot open a QuietGrowth account is because of certain regulations in those countries. In order for QuietGrowth to accept residents of those countries, QuietGrowth needs to follow various extra rules stipulated by those countries, which we does not intend to follow at this point of time.",
			  "url": "faq/Can-a-resident-of-any-country-open-an-account-with-QuietGrowth"
		  , "section": "Creating an account — Residents of other countries" },
		  {
	  "questionkey": "How do you conduct ID verification of clients residing outside Australia",
	  "answerkey": "For a client who mentions that her current residential address is outside Australia we request her to provide us a certified copy of her ID document For details on the nature of the identity document that we request please refer our Certifying the Identification Document webpage",
	  "question": "How do you conduct ID verification of clients residing outside Australia?",
			  "answer": "For a client who mentions that her current residential address is outside Australia, we request her to provide us a certified copy of her ID document. For details on the nature of the identity document that we request, please refer our Certifying the Identification Document webpage.",
			  "url": "faq/How-do-you-conduct-ID-verification-of-clients-residing-outside-Australia"
		  , "section": "Creating an account — Residents of other countries" },
		  {
	  "questionkey": "I do not have a bank account in Australia Can I transfer money from my bank account outside Australia",
	  "answerkey": "Yes You can transfer money from your bank account outside Australia to your brokerage account that is created in your name The default currency for transferring is Australian Dollar AUD Please contact us for information regarding other currency denominated funds transfer If you transfer money that is in a different currency than AUD your money will be accepted and automatically be converted to AUD by our brokerage firm who will charge a non refundable currency conversion fee to you If your money is subsequently rejected by the brokerage firm for example for Third Party Funding or remittances from Exchange Houses Money Changers then any currency conversion already carried out on your money will not be reversed Please contact us for details about the currency conversion fee and currency conversion rates",
	  "question": "I do not have a bank account in Australia. Can I transfer money from my bank account outside Australia?",
			  "answer": "Yes. You can transfer money from your bank account outside Australia to your brokerage account that is created in your name.\n\nThe default currency for transferring is Australian Dollar (AUD). Please contact us for information regarding other currency denominated funds transfer. If you transfer money that is in a different currency than AUD, your money will be accepted and automatically be converted to AUD by our brokerage firm who will charge a non-refundable currency conversion fee to you.\n\nIf your money is subsequently rejected by the brokerage firm (for example, for Third Party Funding or remittances from Exchange Houses/Money Changers), then any currency conversion already carried out on your money will not be reversed.\n\nPlease contact us for details about the currency conversion fee and currency conversion rates.",
			  "url": "faq/I-do-not-have-a-bank-account-in-Australia-Can-I-transfer-money-from-my-bank-account-outside-Australia"
		  , "section": "Creating an account — Residents of other countries" },
		  {
	  "questionkey": "How do I deposit money for investment through QuietGrowth",
	  "answerkey": "A brokerage account will be created for the client during the client onboarding process with QuietGrowth QuietGrowth handles that brokerage account of the client A client can transfer money for investment from her personal bank account to her brokerage account by the following methods Electronic funds transfer EFT using BSB and account number You will be able to perform a funds transfer using the BSB and bank account number that we will provide you at the time of account creation Personal Cheque You will be able to transfer funds by a cheque payable to the account holder that is you the client deposited by you with our brokerage account provider Only personal cheques from Australian citizens or permanent residents of Australia are accepted Only personal cheques for AUD currency are accepted Third party cheques are not accepted Bank Cheques are not accepted Please contact us if you want to opt for transfer through a cheque Below are some additional information As per regulations we do not accept money that originates from a third-party account Money transferred must originate from a bank account under the same name that is in our records We do not accept Banker Drafts Cash Deposits and remittances from Exchange Houses Money Changers Money received from any or all of these payment channels will be rejected and returned to the sender less bank charges if any Currency for transferring is AUD Please contact us for information regarding other currency denominated funds transfer Also read our answer to the question I do not have a bank account in Australia Can I transfer money from my bank account outside Australia",
	  "question": "How do I deposit money for investment through QuietGrowth?",
			  "answer": "A brokerage account will be created for the client during the client onboarding process with QuietGrowth. QuietGrowth handles that brokerage account of the client. A client can transfer money for investment from her personal bank account to her brokerage account by the following methods: Electronic funds transfer (EFT) using BSB and account number: You will be able to perform a funds transfer using the BSB and bank account number that we will provide you at the time of account creation. Personal Cheque: You will be able to transfer funds by a cheque payable to the account holder (that is you, the client) deposited by you with our brokerage account provider. Only personal cheques from Australian citizens or permanent residents of Australia are accepted. Only personal cheques for AUD currency are accepted. Third party cheques are not accepted Bank Cheques are not accepted. Please contact us if you want to opt for transfer through a cheque. Below are some additional information: As per regulations we do not accept money that originates from a third-party account. Money transferred must originate from a bank account under the same name that is in our records. We do not accept Banker Drafts, Cash Deposits and remittances from Exchange Houses/Money Changers. Money received from any or all of these payment channels will be rejected and returned to the sender (less bank charges, if any). Currency for transferring is AUD. Please contact us for information regarding other currency denominated funds transfer. Also read our answer to the question: I do not have a bank account in Australia. Can I transfer money from my bank account outside Australia?",
			  "url": "faq/How-do-I-deposit-money-for-investment-through-QuietGrowth"
		  , "section": "Adding funds" },
		  {
	  "questionkey": "May I transfer my existing securities portfolio to my QuietGrowth account",
	  "answerkey": "Please contact us if you intend to transfer your existing securities portfolio to QuietGrowth Before the transfer you will need to sell all mutual funds bonds and/or equity holdings other than ETF and mutual funds that are part of your QuietGrowth plan",
	  "question": "May I transfer my existing securities portfolio to my QuietGrowth account?",
			  "answer": "Please contact us if you intend to transfer your existing securities portfolio to QuietGrowth. Before the transfer, you will need to sell all mutual funds, bonds and/or equity holdings other than ETFs and mutual funds that are part of your QuietGrowth plan.",
			  "url": "faq/May-I-transfer-my-existing-securities-portfolio-to-my-QuietGrowth-account"
		  , "section": "Adding funds" },
		  {
	  "questionkey": "How do you determine the cash component in my portfolios",
	  "answerkey": "QuietGrowth does not believe in keeping aside a portion of the portfolio value in cash in order to purchase the funds at the right time because we think that it is almost impossible to time the markets consistently That said though QuietGrowth wishes to invest all the money you deposit to purchase the funds we keep aside a small amount of uninvested cash in each of your portfolios for various reasons One reason is that we purchase only whole units of ETFs for you. This results in some amount of cash being left out Another reason is that we ensure that sufficient amount of cash is available to pay for the QuietGrowth fees charged every month over a period of at least one year As the QuietGrowth fees is calculated based on the portfolio value and we cannot predict the future portfolio value the amount of cash we keep aside for this purpose is an approximation One more reason is that even though QuietGrowth absorbs the trading costs incurred to purchase funds and does not charge the client for these costs incurred we are mindful of these costs too and hence we execute a buy trade only when the dollar amount of that trade is of a meaningful amount",
	  "question": "How do you determine the cash component in my portfolios?",
			  "answer": "QuietGrowth does not believe in keeping aside a portion of the portfolio value in cash in order to purchase the funds at the \"right\" time, because we think that it is almost impossible to time the markets consistently. That said, though QuietGrowth wishes to invest all the money you deposit to purchase the funds, we keep aside a small amount of uninvested cash in each of your portfolios for various reasons.\n\nOne reason is that we purchase only whole units of ETFs for you. This results in some amount of cash being left out.\n\nAnother reason is that we ensure that sufficient amount of cash is available to pay for the QuietGrowth fees charged every month over a period of at least one year. As the QuietGrowth fees is calculated based on the portfolio value, and we cannot predict the future portfolio value, the amount of cash we keep aside for this purpose is an approximation.\n\nOne more reason is that even though QuietGrowth absorbs the trading costs incurred to purchase funds and does not charge the client for these costs incurred, we are mindful of these costs too, and hence we execute a buy trade only when the dollar amount of that trade is of a meaningful amount.",
			  "url": "faq/How-do-you-determine-the-cash-component-in-my-portfolios"
		  , "section": "Adding funds" },
		  {
	  "questionkey": "Is there a minimum amount that needs to be added to my QuietGrowth account before the cash in the portfolio is invested in the market",
	  "answerkey": "For total deposits of $10,000 or more in a portfolio Out of the cash that is present in your portfolio we reserve enough cash to cover QuietGrowth’s fees that you would incur typically for a period of one year Then we will consider to invest the rest of your cash in that portfolio in ETFs as soon as that rest of the cash reaches $3,000 For example if the cash in your portfolio is $3100 and the tentative QuietGrowth fees that you would be incurring over the next one year period is $30 then we will consider that the amount available to invest in ETFs is only $3070 and execute one or more buy orders to invest an amount close to $3070 in one or more units of an ETF or ETFs We also follow this same practice if the total deposits in the portfolio has reached $10,000 and then the value of the portfolio has fallen below $10,000 due to withdrawals from that portfolio For total initial deposits less than $10,000 in a portfolio Usually it is unlikely that we will execute a trade if the cash available for investing is less than $300 At the other extreme we will make sure that we execute a trade if the cash available for investing reaches $3300 There is no exact minimum amount that needs to be deposited so that we can execute a trade to invest that amount We will consider various factors such as the number and size of the buy trades that we need to execute so that a fully diversified portfolio is achieved when you deposit a total of $10,000 over one or many fund transfers",
	  "question": "Is there a minimum amount that needs to be added to my QuietGrowth account before the cash in the portfolio is invested in the market?",
			  "answer": "For total deposits of $10,000 or more in a portfolio:\n\nOut of the cash that is present in your portfolio, we reserve enough cash to cover QuietGrowth’s fees that you would incur, typically for a period of one year. Then we will consider to invest the rest of your cash in that portfolio in ETFs as soon as that rest of the cash reaches $3,000.\n\nFor example, if the cash in your portfolio is $3100, and the tentative QuietGrowth fees that you would be incurring over the next one year period is $30, then we will consider that the amount available to invest in ETFs is only $3070 and execute one or more buy orders to invest an amount close to $3070 in one or more units of an ETF or ETFs.\n\nWe also follow this same practice if the total deposits in the portfolio has reached $10,000 and then the value of the portfolio has fallen below $10,000 due to withdrawals from that portfolio.\n\nFor total initial deposits less than $10,000 in a portfolio:\n\nUsually, it is unlikely that we will execute a trade if the cash available for investing is less than $300. At the other extreme, we will make sure that we execute a trade if the cash available for investing reaches $3300.\n\nThere is no exact minimum amount that needs to be deposited so that we can execute a trade to invest that amount.\n\nWe will consider various factors such as the number and size of the buy trades that we need to execute so that a fully diversified portfolio is achieved when you deposit a total of $10,000 over one or many fund transfers.",
			  "url": "faq/Is-there-a-minimum-amount-that-needs-to-be-added-to-my-QuietGrowth-account-before-the-cash-in-the-portfolio-is-invested-in-the-market"
		  , "section": "Adding funds" },
		  {
	  "questionkey": "Is there any minimum amount for subsequent deposits after the minimum initial deposit",
	  "answerkey": "After the minimum initial deposit you can transfer any amount in your subsequent deposits to your QuietGrowth account Also refer our answer to the question What is the minimum amount required to be deposited initially in a QuietGrowth portfolio Please note that we will execute a buy trade only after the cash in the portfolio reaches a certain amount For more information refer our answer to the question Is there a minimum amount that needs to be added to my QuietGrowth account before the cash in the portfolio is invested in the market",
	  "question": "Is there any minimum amount for subsequent deposits, after the minimum initial deposit?",
			  "answer": "After the minimum initial deposit, you can transfer any amount in your subsequent deposits to your QuietGrowth account.\n\nAlso refer our answer to the question \"What is the minimum amount required to be deposited initially in a QuietGrowth portfolio?\"\n\nPlease note that we will execute a buy trade only after the cash in the portfolio reaches a certain amount. For more information, refer our answer to the question \"Is there a minimum amount that needs to be added to my QuietGrowth account before the cash in the portfolio is invested in the market?\"",
			  "url": "faq/Is-there-any-minimum-amount-for-subsequent-deposits-after-the-minimum-initial-deposit"
		  , "section": "Adding funds" },
		  {
	  "questionkey": "What is the difference between depositing money depositing funds transferring funds and contribution to QuietGrowth from the bank account of the client",
	  "answerkey": "They all mean the same Different phrases are used by different clients Also these phrases are used alternately in QuietGrowth website",
	  "question": "What is the difference between depositing money, depositing funds, transferring funds, and contribution to QuietGrowth from the bank account of the client?",
			  "answer": "They all mean the same! Different phrases are used by different clients. Also, these phrases are used alternately in QuietGrowth website.",
			  "url": "faq/What-is-the-difference-between-depositing-money-depositing-funds-transferring-funds-and-contribution-to-QuietGrowth-from-the-bank-account-of-the-client"
		  , "section": "Adding funds" },
		  {
	  "questionkey": "I live outside Australia Do you accept a remittance through a Money Changer",
	  "answerkey": "No we do not accept Banker Drafts Cash Deposits and remittances from Exchange Houses Money Changers Funds received from any or all of these payment channels will be rejected and returned to the sender less bank charges if any",
	  "question": "I live outside Australia. Do you accept a remittance through a Money Changer?",
			  "answer": "No, we do not accept Banker’s Drafts, Cash Deposits and remittances from Exchange Houses/Money Changers. Funds received from any or all of these payment channels will be rejected and returned to the sender (less bank charges, if any).",
			  "url": "faq/I-live-outside-Australia-Do-you-accept-a-remittance-through-a-Money-Changer"
		  , "section": "Adding funds" },
		  {
	  "questionkey": "When will my second or subsequent portfolios have exposure to all the asset classes mentioned in my investment plan",
	  "answerkey": "As long as your total funds deposited for investing in your second portfolio are less than $25000 QuietGrowth phasesin your funds towards purchase of one ETF after the other This is the case for any additional portfolios too That is till the time your invested funds are less than $25000 you will have a partly diversified portfolio only As you invest progressively towards $25000 we will buy more ETF progressively towards your fully diversified second or subsequent portfolio As soon as your deposited funds reach $25000 you will have exposure to the fully diversified QuietGrowth portfolio So it is preferable if you could invest more towards reaching $25000 in deposits in your second or subsequent portfolios Please note that this amount is $10000 only for your first portfolio as explained here",
	  "question": "When will my second or subsequent portfolios have exposure to all the asset classes mentioned in my investment plan?",
			  "answer": "As long as your total funds deposited for investing in your second portfolio are less than $25,000, QuietGrowth phases-in your funds towards purchase of one ETF after the other. This is the case for any additional portfolios too.\n\nThat is, till the time your invested funds are less than $25,000, you will have a partly-diversified portfolio only. As you invest progressively towards $25,000, we will buy more ETFs progressively towards your fully-diversified second or subsequent portfolio. As soon as your deposited funds reach $25,000, you will have exposure to the fully-diversified QuietGrowth portfolio. So, it is preferable if you could invest more towards reaching $25,000 in deposits in your second or subsequent portfolios.\n\nPlease note that this amount is $10,000 only for your first portfolio as explained here.",
			  "url": "faq/When-will-my-second-or-subsequent-portfolios-have-exposure-to-all-the-asset-classes-mentioned-in-my-investment-plan"
		  , "section": "Multiple portfolios" },
		  {
	  "questionkey": "Can I delete a portfolio before I would have gone ahead to invest in it",
	  "answerkey": "Yes you can rollback the creation of your second and subsequent portfolios if you have not yet invested money in them",
	  "question": "Can I delete a portfolio before I would have gone ahead to invest in it?",
			  "answer": "Yes, you can rollback the creation of your second and subsequent portfolios, if you have not yet invested money in them.",
			  "url": "faq/Can-I-delete-a-portfolio-before-I-would-have-gone-ahead-to-invest-in-it"
		  , "section": "Multiple portfolios" },
		  {
	  "questionkey": "How does QuietGrowth choose which ETFs to sell when I place a withdraw request",
	  "answerkey": "In order to execute the withdrawal request QuietGrowth liquidates the investments made in various ETF We will attempt to sell ETF units in such a manner to both minimize your tax liability from the withdrawal and to rebalance your portfolio towards your target allocation in the Investment Plan",
	  "question": "How does QuietGrowth choose which ETFs to sell when I place a withdraw request?",
			  "answer": "In order to execute the withdrawal request, QuietGrowth liquidates the investments made in various ETFs. We will attempt to sell ETF units in such a manner to both minimize your tax liability from the withdrawal, and to rebalance your portfolio towards your target allocation in the Investment Plan.",
			  "url": "faq/How-does-QuietGrowth-choose-which-ETFs-to-sell-when-I-place-a-withdraw-request"
		  , "section": "Withdrawals" },
		  {
	  "questionkey": "I have set up fingerprint security as well as two factor authentication for my QuietGrowth mobile app Will both of them work simultaneously",
	  "answerkey": "If you have set up the fingerprint security as well as two factor authentication for your QuietGrowth app iOS or Android then the fingerprint security will be considered automatically by the app However if you log in to your account through the QuietGrowth website then the twofactor authentication will be considered",
	  "question": "I have set up fingerprint security as well as two-factor authentication for my QuietGrowth mobile app. Will both of them work simultaneously?",
			  "answer": "If you have set up the fingerprint security as well as two-factor authentication for your QuietGrowth app (iOS or Android), then the fingerprint security will be considered automatically by the app. However, if you log in to your account through the QuietGrowth website, then the two-factor authentication will be considered.",
			  "url": "faq/Fingerprint-security-as-well-as-two-factor-authentication-for-my-QuietGrowth-mobile-app"
		  , "section": "Security" },
		  {
	  "questionkey": "What components of client data does the brokerage firm has access to",
	  "answerkey": "QuietGrowth will not share with the brokerage firm any client data that is not necessary for them to perform their tasks The brokerage firm will have access to all your trading data They will also have access to your profile details that are necessary for Know Your Client KYC and Anti Money Laundering AML compliance requirements and for brokerage account opening and account maintenance requirements The brokerage firm will not have access to other data of yours nor will they have access to the financial advice that QuietGrowth provides to you",
	  "question": "What components of client data does the brokerage firm has access to?",
			  "answer": "QuietGrowth will not share with the brokerage firm any client data that is not necessary for them to perform their tasks.\n\nThe brokerage firm will have access to all your trading data. They will also have access to your profile details that are necessary for Know Your Client (KYC) and Anti Money Laundering (AML) compliance requirements, and for brokerage account opening and account maintenance requirements. The brokerage firm will not have access to other data of yours, nor will they have access to the financial advice that QuietGrowth provides to you.",
			  "url": "faq/What-components-of-client-data-does-the-brokerage-firm-has-access-to"
		  , "section": "Security" },
		  {
			  "questionkey": "Do you sell my data",
			  "answerkey": "No We do not sell your data to third parties We make money by charging you QuietGrowth fees for our services to you Please refer to our Privacy Policy for more information",
			  "question": "Do you sell my data?",
			  "answer": "No. We do not sell your data to third parties. We make money by charging you QuietGrowth fees for our services to you.\n\nPlease refer to our 'Privacy Policy' for more information.",
			   "section": "Security" 
		  },
		  {
	  "questionkey": "Do you provide general financial advice or personal financial advice",
	  "answerkey": "We provide both general financial advice as well as personal financial advice limited to the suitability of client to the Managed Discretionary Account MDA service of QuietGrowth The financial information that we provide in our website and in other mediums by not taking into consideration your personal circumstances is the general financial advice The financial information that we provide by taking into consideration your personal circumstances is the personal financial advice The personal financial advice that we provide is through our Managed Discretionary Account MDA service",
	  "question": "Do you provide general financial advice or personal financial advice?",
			  "answer": "We provide both general financial advice as well as personal financial advice limited to the suitability of client to the Managed Discretionary Account (MDA) service of QuietGrowth.\n\nThe financial information that we provide in our website and in other mediums by not taking into consideration your personal circumstances, is the general financial advice.\n\nThe financial information that we provide by taking into consideration your personal circumstances is the personal financial advice. The personal financial advice that we provide is through our Managed Discretionary Account (MDA) service.",
			  "url": "faq/Do-you-provide-general-financial-advice-or-personal-financial-advice"
		  , "section": "Structure of QuietGrowth service" },
		  {
	  "questionkey": "Is the financial advice that you provide separate from the MDA service that you provide",
	  "answerkey": "The financial advice that we provide is part of the Managed Discretionary Account MDA service that we provide",
	  "question": "Is the financial advice that you provide separate from the MDA service that you provide?",
			  "answer": "The financial advice that we provide is part of the Managed Discretionary Account (MDA) service that we provide.",
			  "url": "faq/Is-the-financial-advice-that-you-provide-separate-from-the-MDA-service-that-you-provide"
		  , "section": "Structure of QuietGrowth service" },
		  {
	  "questionkey": "Through what structure does QuietGrowth offer its service to me",
	  "answerkey": "We provide you the QuietGrowth service through the Managed Discretionary Account MDA structure",
	  "question": "Through what structure does QuietGrowth offer its service to me?",
			  "answer": "We provide you the QuietGrowth service through the Managed Discretionary Account (MDA) structure.",
			  "url": "faq/Through-what-structure-does-QuietGrowth-offer-its-service-to-me"
		  , "section": "Structure of QuietGrowth service" },
		  {
	  "questionkey": "What are the documents you provide to me before my account is created",
	  "answerkey": "As a part of your on-boarding process before your QuietGrowth account is created we will provide you the digital copies of the following documents Statement of Advice SOA Investment Program Financial Services Guide Client Agreement and Managed Discretionary Account MDA Application",
	  "question": "What are the documents you provide to me before my account is created?",
			  "answer": "As a part of your on-boarding process, before your QuietGrowth account is created, we will provide you the digital copies of the following documents:\n\n•  Statement of Advice (SOA)\n\n•  Investment Program\n\n•  Financial Services Guide\n\n•  Client Agreement, and\n\n•  Managed Discretionary Account (MDA) Application",
			  "url": "faq/What-are-the-documents-you-provide-to-me-before-my-account-is-created"
		  , "section": "Structure of QuietGrowth service" },
		  {
	  "questionkey": "Is QuietGrowth an online discretionary investment manager ODIM",
	  "answerkey": "YesQuietGrowth is an online discretionary investment manager ODIM Our QuietGrowth service is an automated investment management service We provide you the QuietGrowth service through the Managed Discretionary Account MDA structure.",
	  "question": "Is QuietGrowth an online discretionary investment manager (ODIM)?",
			  "answer": "Yes, QuietGrowth is an online discretionary investment manager (ODIM). Our QuietGrowth service is an automated investment management service. We provide you the QuietGrowth service through the Managed Discretionary Account (MDA) structure.",
			  "url": "faq/Is-QuietGrowth-an-online-discretionary-investment-manager-ODIM"
		  , "section": "Structure of QuietGrowth service" },
		  {
	  "questionkey": "Is QuietGrowth a do-it-yourself DIY service or a do-it-for-me DIFM service",
	  "answerkey": "QuietGrowth is a do it for me DIFM service. We are not a do it yourself DIY service You delegate to QuietGrowth the task of managing the money that you deposit We provide you the QuietGrowth service through the Managed Discretionary Account MDA structure",
	  "question": "Is QuietGrowth a do-it-yourself (DIY) service or a do-it-for-me (DIFM) service?",
			  "answer": "QuietGrowth is a do-it-for-me (DIFM) service. We are not a do-it-yourself (DIY) service.\n\nYou delegate to QuietGrowth the task of managing the money that you deposit. We provide you the QuietGrowth service through the Managed Discretionary Account (MDA) structure.",
			  "url": "faq/Is-QuietGrowth-a-do-it-yourself-DIY-service-or-a-do-it-for-me-DIFM-service"
		  , "section": "Structure of QuietGrowth service" },
		  {
	  "questionkey": "Is QuietGrowth a digital only roboadviser or a hybrid roboadviser",
	  "answerkey": "We are a digital only roboadviser We are not a hybrid roboadviser A hybrid roboadviser includes a human financial adviser providing financial advice to a client face to face over phone or over online chat However a digital only roboadvisor does not include client interaction with a human financial adviser",
	  "question": "Is QuietGrowth a digital-only roboadviser or a hybrid roboadviser?",
			  "answer": "We are a digital-only roboadviser. We are not a hybrid roboadviser.\n\nA hybrid roboadviser includes a human financial adviser providing financial advice to a client face-to-face, over phone or over online chat. However, a digital-only roboadvisor does not include client interaction with a human financial adviser.",
			  "url": "faq/Is-QuietGrowth-a-digital-only-roboadviser-or-a-hybrid-roboadviser"
		  , "section": "Structure of QuietGrowth service" },
		  {
	  "questionkey": "What are the advantages of Managed Discretionary Account MDA structure through which you offer your service",
	  "answerkey": "QuietGrowth provides its service through the Managed Discretionary Account MDA structure to enable clients to delegate the investment management and trading discretion for exchange traded funds and other securities to QuietGrowth This means QuietGrowth will invest in financial products on your behalf without prior reference to you for each individual transaction Investing through an MDA allows you to retain beneficial ownership of the underlying securities By the term beneficial ownership we mean that you retain the benefits of ownership similar to the manner of you owning directly the underlying securities The benefits of ownership include dividends and franking credits",
	  "question": "What are the advantages of Managed Discretionary Account (MDA) structure through which you offer your service?",
			  "answer": "QuietGrowth provides its service through the Managed Discretionary Account (MDA) structure to enable clients to delegate the investment management and trading discretion for exchange traded funds and other securities to QuietGrowth. This means QuietGrowth will invest in financial products on your behalf without prior reference to you for each individual transaction.\n\nInvesting through an MDA allows you to retain beneficial ownership of the underlying securities. By the term beneficial ownership, we mean that you retain the benefits of ownership similar to the manner of you owning directly the underlying securities. The benefits of ownership include dividends and franking credits.",
			  "url": "faq/What-are-the-advantages-of-Managed-Discretionary-Account-MDA-structure-through-which-you-offer-your-service"
		  , "section": "Structure of QuietGrowth service" },
		  {
	  "questionkey": "Is my QuietGrowth account a managed account or a managed fund",
	  "answerkey": "Your QuietGrowth account is a Managed Discretionary Account MDA Soit is also a managed account because an MDA is a subset of managed accounts Your QuietGrowth account is not a managed fund",
	  "question": "Is my QuietGrowth account a managed account or a managed fund?",
			  "answer": "Your QuietGrowth account is a Managed Discretionary Account (MDA). So, it is also a managed account because an MDA is a subset of managed accounts. Your QuietGrowth account is not a managed fund.",
			  "url": "faq/Is-my-QuietGrowth-account-a-managed-account-or-a-managed-fund"
		  , "section": "Structure of QuietGrowth service" },
		  {
	  "questionkey": "Do each of my QuietGrowth portfolios constitute separate instances of Managed Discretionary Accounts",
	  "answerkey": "No All your QuietGrowth portfolios in your QuietGrowth account constitute one single Managed Discretionary Account MDA in your name",
	  "question": "Do each of my QuietGrowth portfolios constitute separate instances of Managed Discretionary Accounts?",
			  "answer": "No. All your QuietGrowth portfolios in your QuietGrowth account constitute one single Managed Discretionary Account (MDA) in your name.",
			  "url": "faq/Do-each-of-my-QuietGrowth-portfolios-constitute-separate-instances-of-Managed-Discretionary-Accounts"
		  , "section": "Structure of QuietGrowth service" },
		  {
	  "questionkey": "Can I invest in QuietGrowth portfolios directly without signing the Managed Discretionary Account contract",
	  "answerkey": "No We provide you the QuietGrowth service through the Managed Discretionary Account MDA structure So you would need to take the risk tolerance determination questionnaire and sign the MDA contract digitally so that we can start managing the money that you transfer to your QuietGrowth portfolios This is as per the regulations",
	  "question": "Can I invest in QuietGrowth portfolios directly without signing the Managed Discretionary Account contract?",
			  "answer": "No. We provide you the QuietGrowth service through the Managed Discretionary Account (MDA) structure. So, you would need to take the risk tolerance determination questionnaire and sign the MDA contract digitally, so that we can start managing the money that you transfer to your QuietGrowth portfolios. This is as per the regulations.",
			  "url": "faq/Can-I-invest-in-QuietGrowth-portfolios-directly-without-signing-the-Managed-Discretionary-Account-contract"
		  , "section": "Structure of QuietGrowth service" },
		  {
	  "questionkey": "Is my QuietGrowth account a Separately Managed Account SMA",
	  "answerkey": "Your QuietGrowth account is not a Separately Managed Account SMA We provide you the QuietGrowth service through the Managed Discretionary Account MDA structure",
	  "question": "Is my QuietGrowth account a Separately Managed Account (SMA)?",
			  "answer": "Your QuietGrowth account is not a Separately Managed Account (SMA). We provide you the QuietGrowth service through the Managed Discretionary Account (MDA) structure.",
			  "url": "faq/Is-my-QuietGrowth-account-a-Separately-Managed-Account-SMA"
		  , "section": "Structure of QuietGrowth service" },
		  {
	  "questionkey": "What is the fee charged by QuietGrowth for its service",
	  "answerkey": "QuietGrowth does not charge its fee on the first $10000 of assets under management On amounts over $10000 we charge a monthly fee based on an annual fee rate ranging from 0.4 to 0.6 which is based on assets under management of the client",
	  "question": "What is the fee charged by QuietGrowth for its service?",
			  "answer": "QuietGrowth does not charge its fee on the first $10,000 of assets under management. On amounts over $10,000, we charge a monthly fee based on an annual fee rate ranging from 0.4% to 0.6%, which is based on assets under management of the client.",
			  "url": "faq/What-is-the-fee-charged-by-QuietGrowth-for-its-service"
		  , "section": "Fees" },
		  {
	  "questionkey": "How are QuietGrowth fees calculated",
			  "answerkey": "Each month you are charged QuietGrowth fee equal to the sum of QuietGrowth fee incurred for each day of that month QuietGrowth fee incurred for each day is equal to 1/365 1/366 on a leap year of the annual rate multiplied by the portfolio value over $10000 as of close of markets for that day Example Shirley invests $109000 in a diversified portfolio in QuietGrowth Shirley begins investing on April 3rd Lets assume that the end of the day portfolio value on April 3rd is $110000 QuietGrowth annual fee rate is 0.5 for $110000 invested As QuietGrowth does not charge annual fee on the first $10000 of the investment Shirley QuietGrowth fee will be calculated only for the managed assets greater than $10000 that is $100000 Therefore Shirley QuietGrowth fee for April 3rd equals Lets assume that the end of the day portfolio value on April 4th is $112000 Shirley QuietGrowth fee for April 4th equals At the end of April month QuietGrowth fee for that month will be charged from her portfolio",
			  
	  "question": "How are QuietGrowth fees calculated?",
			  "answer": "Each month you are charged QuietGrowth fee equal to the sum of QuietGrowth fee incurred for each day of that month. QuietGrowth fee incurred for each day is equal to 1/365 (1/366 on a leap year) of the annual rate multiplied by the portfolio value over $10,000 as of close of markets for that day.\n\nExample:\nShirley invests $109,000 in a diversified portfolio in QuietGrowth. Shirley begins investing on April 3rd. Let’s assume that the end-of-the-day portfolio value on April 3rd is $110,000. QuietGrowth’s annual fee rate is 0.5% for $110,000 invested. As QuietGrowth does not charge annual fee on the first $10,000 of the investment, Shirley's QuietGrowth fee will be calculated only for the managed assets greater than $10,000, that is $100,000.\n\nTherefore, Shirley’s QuietGrowth fee for April 3rd equals: (0.5% / 365) * (the portfolio value greater than $10,000) = (0.5% / 365) * $100,000 = $1.36986301.\n\nLet’s assume that the end-of-the-day portfolio value on April 4th is $112,000. Shirley’s QuietGrowth fee for April 4th equals: (0.5% / 365) * $102,000 = $1.39726027.\n\nAt the end of April month, QuietGrowth fee for that month will be charged from her portfolio.",
			  "url": "faq/How-are-QuietGrowth-fees-calculated"
		  , "section": "Fees" },
		  {
	  "questionkey": "When does QuietGrowth charge its fee",
	  "answerkey": "QuietGrowth fee for a particular calendar month are usually charged on the first business day of the following month For example the QuietGrowth fee for investing during the month of May 2013 was charged on June 3 2013 the first business day of June",
	  "question": "When does QuietGrowth charge its fee?",
			  "answer": "QuietGrowth fee for a particular calendar month are usually charged on the first business day of the following month. For example, the QuietGrowth fee for investing during the month of May 2013 was charged on June 3, 2013 (the first business day of June).",
			  "url": "faq/When-does-QuietGrowth-charge-its-fee"
		  , "section": "Fees" },
		  {
	  "questionkey": "How much should I invest through QuietGrowth",
	  "answerkey": "You can invest all your savings for the long term in the QuietGrowth portfolios as per the advice we provide you in our Statement of Advice after you set aside the requisite money for rainy day fund in term deposits low-risk fixed income instruments or cash If the rainy day fund comprises of a small portion of higher risk equity exposure then such instrument should be highly diversified It should cover at least six months of expenses to deal with any unexpected emergencies such as unemployment illness that might arise in your life as well as in your dependent family members lives The rainy day fund would also include six month worth of any monthly payment commitments that you might be having towards mortgages loans and insurance premiums an optional discretionary fund of a size that you are comfortable with if you have the financial strength and appetite to easily withstand the loss of that entire amount in the worst case scenario The amount in this discretionary fund can go towards investing in risky opportunities in which you personally believe and understand such as a specific stock a personal loan for a relatively higher interest to a friend or a business venture of your friend After you set aside the requisite money for a rainy day fund and an optional discretionary fund we believe that you need to invest the rest in a highly diversified risk optimised portfolio for the long term This is where you can consider QuietGrowth",
	  "question": "How much should I invest through QuietGrowth?",
			  "answer": "You can invest all your savings for the long term in the QuietGrowth portfolios, as per the advice we provide you in our 'Statement of Advice', after you set aside the requisite money for:\n\na 'rainy-day fund' in term deposits, low-risk fixed-income instruments or cash. If the rainy-day fund comprises of a small portion of higher-risk equity exposure, then such instruments should be highly-diversified. It should cover at least six months of expenses to deal with any unexpected emergencies (such as unemployment, illness) that might arise in your life as well as in your dependent family members' lives. The rainy-day fund would also include six-month's worth of any monthly payment commitments that you might be having towards mortgages, loans and insurance premiums.\nan optional 'discretionary fund', of a size that you are comfortable with, if you have the financial strength and appetite to easily withstand the loss of that entire amount in the worst-case scenario. The amount in this discretionary fund can go towards investing in risky opportunities in which you personally believe and understand, such as a specific stock, a personal loan for a relatively-higher interest to a friend, or a business venture of your friend.\nAfter you set aside the requisite money for a 'rainy-day fund' and an optional 'discretionary fund', we believe that you need to invest the rest in a highly diversified, risk-optimised portfolio for the long-term. This is where you can consider QuietGrowth.",
			  "url": "faq/How-much-should-I-invest-through-QuietGrowth",
			  "section": "General questions"
	   },
		  {
	  "questionkey": "What is the historical performance of your portfolios",
	  "answerkey": "You can view the historical performance of our risk adjusted portfolios in the Why QuietGrowth page After you take our questionnaire to evaluate your risk tolerance score you can also compare the historical performance of the portfolio that we suggest to you with that of benchmarks of various asset classes",
	  "question": "What is the historical performance of your portfolios?",
			  "answer": "You can view the historical performance of our risk-adjusted portfolios in the “Why QuietGrowth” page. After you take our questionnaire to evaluate your risk tolerance score, you can also compare the historical performance of the portfolio that we suggest to you with that of benchmarks of various asset classes.",
			  "url": "faq/What-is-the-historical-performance-of-your-portfolios"
		  , "section": "General questions" },
		  {
	  "questionkey": "Why dont you display 1-year and 3-year portfolio returns in addition to 10-year returns",
	  "answerkey": "The investment methodology of QuietGrowth Portfolios is long term oriented This is the reason for us to display a ten 10 year historical return chart in the website and to not calculate explicitly the one 1 year or three 3 year historical returns This is part of our attempt to communicate to the clients that they should consider their investing in QuietGrowth portfolios with a long term perspective That said if you are inclined to know the one 1 year or three 3 year returns of QuietGrowth Portfolios you can calculate that by picking the required data for the specific time period from the ten 10 year historical performance chart in the QuietGrowth website",
	  "question": "Why don’t you display 1-year and 3-year portfolio returns, in addition to 10-year returns?",
			  "answer": "The investment methodology of QuietGrowth Portfolios is long-term oriented. This is the reason for us to display a 10-year historical return chart in the website, and to not calculate explicitly the 1-year or 3-year historical returns. This is part of our attempt to communicate to the clients that they should consider their investing in QuietGrowth portfolios with a long-term perspective.\n\nThat said, if you are inclined to know the 1-year or 3-year returns of QuietGrowth Portfolios, you can calculate that by picking the required data for the specific time-period from the 10-year historical performance chart in the QuietGrowth website.",
			  "url": "faq/Why-dont-you-display-1-year-and-3-year-portfolio-returns-in-addition-to-10-year-returns"
		  , "section": "General questions" },
		  {
	  "questionkey": "How do you calculate the return on investments",
	  "answerkey": "We calcuate the return on investments using Time Weighed Return TWR We also use Money weighted return There are different methods to calculate returns such as Time weighted return Money weighted return Internal rate of return and Simple return Among these we believe that the Time weighted return is the best method Annualized Internal rate of return is another name for Money weighted return We do not use unannualized Internal rate of return as it is not most suitable We do not suggest using the Simple return TWR is the compound rate of daily return TWR shows how effectively QuietGrowth has managed your investments It does not consider when you have executed your deposits and withdrawals and this should be the case if we need to measure the performance of QuietGrowth Moreover it is preferable that the performance of QuietGrowth portfolios is calculated similar to the manner in which the performance of an index fund is calculated and TWR is used by index funds",
	  "question": "How do you calculate the return on investments?",
			  "answer": "We calcuate the return on investments using Time-Weighed Return (TWR). We also use Money-weighted return.\n\nThere are different methods to calculate returns such as Time-weighted return, Money-weighted return, Internal rate of return and Simple return. Among these, we believe that the Time-weighted return is the best method. Annualized Internal rate of return is another name for Money-weighted return. We do not use unannualized Internal rate of return as it is not most suitable. We do not suggest using the Simple return.\n\nTWR is the compound rate of daily return. TWR shows how effectively QuietGrowth has managed your investments. It does not consider when you have executed your deposits and withdrawals, and this should be the case if we need to measure the performance of QuietGrowth. Moreover it is preferable that the performance of QuietGrowth portfolios is calculated similar to the manner in which the performance of an index fund is calculated, and TWR is used by index funds.",
			  "url": "faq/How-do-you-calculate-the-return-on-investments"
		  , "section": "General questions" },
		  {
	  "questionkey": "Who owns QuietGrowth",
	  "answerkey": "QuietGrowth is founded by individuals who are passionate about transforming how people invest The founding team members have a significant ownership Various high net worth individuals are minority shareholders",
	  "question": "Who owns QuietGrowth?",
			  "answer": "QuietGrowth is founded by individuals who are passionate about transforming how people invest. The founding team members have a significant ownership. Various high-net worth individuals are minority shareholders.",
			  "url": "faq/Who-owns-QuietGrowth"
		  , "section": "General questions" },
		  {
	  "questionkey": "When was QuietGrowth established",
	  "answerkey": "We established as a firm in 2014 and have been managing the investments of our clients since October 2015",
	  "question": "When was QuietGrowth established?",
			  "answer": "We established as a firm in 2014, and have been managing the investments of our clients since October 2015.",
			  "url": "faq/When-was-QuietGrowth-established"
		  , "section": "General questions" },
		  {
	  "questionkey": "Do you provide the micro investing service",
	  "answerkey": "No We do not provide the micro investing service However a client can deposit any amount any number of times to their QuietGrowth portfolio We are referring to the following use case when we speak about a typical micro investing service if a client makes a purchase then the spare change of the round up transaction amount gets automatically deposited to their portfolio in a micro investing service We opine that micro investing can be a good temporary option for first time investors who are starting to understand the world of investing However we are aiming to serve clients who are investing for the long term AFTER they have set up their rainy-day fund in cash or term deposits to cover at least six months of expenses to deal with any unexpected emergencies unemployment illness that might arise in your as well as your family member lives this would also include six-months worth of any monthly payment commitments that you might be having for your investment in mortgages or loans Please refer to our Micro Investing knowledge resource for more information",
	  "question": "Do you provide the micro-investing service?",
			  "answer": "No. We do not provide the micro-investing service. However, a client can deposit any amount, any number of times, to their QuietGrowth portfolio.\n\nWe are referring to the following use case when we speak about a typical micro-investing service: if a client makes a purchase, then the spare change of the round-up transaction amount gets automatically deposited to their portfolio in a micro-investing service.\n\nWe opine that micro-investing can be a good temporary option for first-time investors who are starting to understand the world of investing. However, we are aiming to serve clients who are investing for the long-term AFTER they have set up their 'rainy-day fund' in cash or term deposits to cover at least six months of expenses to deal with any unexpected emergencies (unemployment, illness, etc.) that might arise in your as well as your family member's lives (this would also include six-months worth of any monthly payment commitments that you might be having for your investment in mortgages or loans).\n\nPlease refer to our 'Micro Investing' knowledge resource for more information.",
			  "url": "faq/Do-you-provide-the-micro-investing-service"
		  , "section": "General questions" },
		  {
	  "questionkey": "What is Navigate money",
	  "answerkey": "Navigate money is an initiative by QuietGrowth to impart financial education to all through effective content Illustrations interactive interfaces interactive visualisations videos and storytelling are some of the methods employed to enable everyone to plan and act better regarding their finances As we want everyone from different occupations and backgrounds to benefit from our content we have ensured that some of our content is of beginner level of comprehension Navigate money is one of our efforts towards our mission to provide access to wise investing to all through knowledge technology and transparency",
	  "question": "What is 'Navigate money'?",
			  "answer": "Navigate money' is an initiative by QuietGrowth to impart financial education to all through effective content. Illustrations, interactive interfaces, interactive visualisations, videos and storytelling are some of the methods employed to enable everyone to plan and act better regarding their finances. As we want everyone, from different occupations and backgrounds to benefit from our content, we have ensured that some of our content is of beginner’s level of comprehension. ‘Navigate money’ is one of our efforts towards our mission to provide access to wise investing to all, through knowledge, technology and transparency.",
			  "url": "faq/What-is-Navigate-money"
		  , "section": "General questions" },
		  {
	  "questionkey": "What is QuietGrowth mission",
	  "answerkey": "Our mission is to provide access to wise investing to all through knowledge technology and transparency",
	  "question": "What is QuietGrowth's mission?",
			  "answer": "Our mission is to provide access to wise investing to all, through knowledge, technology and transparency.",
			  "url": "faq/What-is-QuietGrowths-mission"
		  , "section": "General questions" },
		  {
	  "questionkey": "What is the mode of communication with your clients",
	  "answerkey": "The mode of communication with our clients regarding information about our service personal financial advice general financial advice accountrelated tasks and technical help are through our website mobile apps and emails We are a digital investment management service through online interactive interfaces Unless there is an issue that requires us to speak with the client we do not communicate with clients over the phone",
	  "question": "What is the mode of communication with your clients?",
	  "answer": "The mode of communication with our clients regarding information about our service, personal financial advice, general financial advice, account-related tasks and technical help are through our website, mobile apps and emails.\n\nWe are a digital investment management service through online interactive interfaces. Unless there is an issue that requires us to speak with the client, we do not communicate with clients over the phone.",
	  "url": "faq/What-is-the-mode-of-communication-with-your-clients"
		  , "section": "General questions" },
		  {
	  "questionkey": "How do you select the ETF in your portfolios",
	  "answerkey": "The first step in our investment methodology is to identify a broad set of diversified asset classes As one of the later steps we select the ETF in each of these asset classes We prefer ETFs with low annual expense ratios minimal tracking error low bid/ask spread costs sufficient liquidity and minimal lending of the underlying securities of the ETFs For detailed information please refer to our Investment Methodology",
	  "question": "How do you select the ETFs in your portfolios?",
			  "answer": "The first step in our investment methodology is to identify a broad set of diversified asset classes. As one of the later steps, we select the ETFs in each of these asset classes. We prefer ETFs with low annual expense ratios, minimal tracking error, low bid/ask spread costs, sufficient liquidity and minimal lending of the underlying securities of the ETFs.\n\nFor detailed information, please refer to our Investment Methodology.",
			  "url": "faq/How-do-you-select-the-ETFs-in-your-portfolios"
		  , "section": "Your Investment Plan" },
		  {
	  "questionkey": "Why do all your portfolios have the same ETF",
	  "answerkey": "For optimal risk adjusted returns the determination of various asset classes and the computation of the most appropriate mix of those asset classes is important ETF only represent those asset classes so that investments can be made in those asset classes through those ETF For everyone the same set of asset classes are applicable For everyone with the same risk tolerance score the same mix of those asset classes applies Then we will choose the most appropriate ETFs that represent each of those asset classes Here again as the asset classes are same for everyone the ETFs that represent those asset classes are the same for everyone",
	  "question": "Why do all your portfolios have the same ETFs?",
			  "answer": "For optimal risk-adjusted returns, the determination of various asset classes and the computation of the most appropriate mix of those asset classes is important. ETFs only represent those asset classes so that investments can be made in those asset classes through those ETFs.\n\nFor everyone, the same set of asset classes are applicable. For everyone with the same risk tolerance score, the same mix of those asset classes applies. Then we will choose the most appropriate ETFs that represent each of those asset classes. Here again, as the asset classes are same for everyone, the ETFs that represent those asset classes are the same for everyone.",
			  "url": "faq/Why-do-all-your-portfolios-have-the-same-ETFs"
		  , "section": "Your Investment Plan" },
		  {
	  "questionkey": "When do you rebalance my portfolios",
	  "answerkey": "We rebalance your portfolio periodically whenever we see that any one of the funds in your portfolio has drifted by a certain percentage from its target allocation that is mentioned in your Investment Program Hence the trigger to rebalance is determined by threshold based percentage drift which we believe is preferable instead of on a predetermined period based such as once every quarter or once every year We will also consider various other aspects before we rebalance such as the cash available to rebalance the prospect and the size of any oncoming dividends the volatility of each fund in your portfolio and the impact on capital gains taxation because of rebalancing Even though QuietGrowth absorbs the trading costs incurred while rebalancing and does not charge the client for these costs incurred we are mindful of these costs too and hence we rebalance only when the dollar amount of the buy or sell trades to be executed while rebalancing is of a meaningful amount We will be monitoring your portfolio for rebalancing on a continual basis Whenever you deposit funds or instruct us to withdraw funds we will also evaluate whether we can perform threshhold based rebalancing at that time as we determine the exact buy or sell trades of various funds that we might execute That is we will try to perform interim rebalancing at each of these instances The relative performance of each of the funds in your portfolio matters a lot towards rebalancing and hence we cannot predict when we are likely to rebalance your portfolio You will be able to see in your dashboard by how much percentage each of your funds has drifted from its target allocation",
	  "question": "When do you rebalance my portfolios?",
			  "answer": "We rebalance your portfolio periodically whenever we see that any one of the funds in your portfolio has drifted by a certain percentage from its target allocation that is mentioned in your Investment Program. Hence the trigger to rebalance is determined by threshold based percentage drift, which we believe is preferable, instead of on a predetermined period based (such as, once every quarter or once every year).\n\nWe will also consider various other aspects before we rebalance, such as the cash available to rebalance, the prospect and the size of any oncoming dividends, the volatility of each fund in your portfolio, and the impact on capital gains taxation because of rebalancing. Even though QuietGrowth absorbs the trading costs incurred while rebalancing and does not charge the client for these costs incurred, we are mindful of these costs too, and hence we rebalance only when the dollar amount of the buy or sell trades to be executed while rebalancing is of a meaningful amount.\n\nWe will be monitoring your portfolio for rebalancing on a continual basis. Whenever you deposit funds or instruct us to withdraw funds, we will also evaluate whether we can perform threshhold-based rebalancing at that time as we determine the exact buy or sell trades of various funds that we might execute. That is, we will try to perform interim rebalancing at each of these instances.\n\nThe relative performance of each of the funds in your portfolio matters a lot towards rebalancing, and hence we cannot predict when we are likely to rebalance your portfolio. You will be able to see in your dashboard by how much percentage each of your funds has drifted from its target allocation.",
			  "url": "faq/When-do-you-rebalance-my-portfolios"
		  , "section": "Your Investment Plan" },
		  {
	  "questionkey": "Do you offer a balanced portfolio",
	  "answerkey": "We offer five different risk portfolios Each of our portfolios is optimised to a specific risk profile of the client The risk of our portfolios ranges from lower risk to higher risk and the five portfolios are named as 1/5 2/5 3/5 4/5 and 5/5 in increasing order of risk You can consider our QuietGrowth Portfolio 3/5 as a balanced portfolio among our list of portfolios because the risk of this portfolio is in the middle of the risk spectrum of QuietGrowth portfolios",
	  "question": "Do you offer a balanced portfolio?",
			  "answer": "We offer five different risk portfolios. Each of our portfolios is optimised to a specific risk profile of the client. The risk of our portfolios ranges from lower risk to higher risk, and the five portfolios are named as 1/5, 2/5, 3/5, 4/5 and 5/5 in increasing order of risk.\n\nYou can consider our QuietGrowth Portfolio 3/5 as a ‘balanced portfolio’ among our list of portfolios, because the risk of this portfolio is in the middle of the risk spectrum of QuietGrowth portfolios.",
			  "url": "faq/Do-you-offer-a-balanced-portfolio"
		  , "section": "Your Investment Plan" },
		  {
	  "questionkey": "How can I invest my superannuation through QuietGrowth",
	  "answerkey": "You can invest your superannuation through your self managed super fund SMSF As of now unless you have set up your SMSF you cannot invest your superannuation through QuietGrowth Refer to our Robo Advice for your SMSF webpage for more information",
	  "question": "How can I invest my superannuation through QuietGrowth?",
			  "answer": "You can invest your superannuation through your self-managed super fund (SMSF). As of now, unless you have set up your SMSF, you cannot invest your superannuation through QuietGrowth. Refer to our Robo Advice for your SMSF webpage for more information.",
			  "url": "faq/How-can-I-invest-my-superannuation-through-QuietGrowth"
		  , "section": "Your Investment Plan" },
		  {
	  "questionkey": "Do you include hedge funds in QuietGrowth Portfolios",
	  "answerkey": "No we do not include hedge funds in QuietGrowth Portfolios as of now Not all hedge funds are equal and it is not preferable to invest in a hedge fund just because that fund happens to be a hedge fund Like most of the other alternate investment opportunities it is prudent to stay away from most of hedge funds except for certain hedge funds that are best in class However it is difficult to participate in such high quality hedge funds especially with favourable terms of participation so that the interests of QuietGrowth clients are catered to So whenever QuietGrowth gets an opportunity to participate with favourable terms in these high quality hedge funds we will certainly consider",
	  "question": "Do you include hedge funds in QuietGrowth Portfolios?",
			  "answer": "No, we do not include hedge funds in QuietGrowth Portfolios, as of now.\n\nNot all hedge funds are equal, and it is not preferable to invest in a hedge fund, just because that fund happens to be a hedge fund. Like most of the other alternate investment opportunities, it is prudent to stay away from most of hedge funds, except for certain hedge funds that are best-in-class. However, it is difficult to participate in such high-quality hedge funds, especially with favourable terms of participation so that the interests of QuietGrowth clients are catered to. So, whenever QuietGrowth gets an opportunity to participate with favourable terms in these high-quality hedge funds, we will certainly consider.",
			  "url": "faq/Do-you-include-hedge-funds-in-QuietGrowth-Portfolios"
		  , "section": "Your Investment Plan" },
		  {
	  "questionkey": "Do you offer direct indexing",
	  "answerkey": "No we do not offer direct indexing as of now The innovation of direct indexing by automated investment management services has emerged in the US since 2015 We are positive about this Using this method QuietGrowth can opt for individual stocks instead of ETFs We at QuietGrowth will not be introducing this at least for sometime",
	  "question": "Do you offer direct indexing?",
			  "answer": "No, we do not offer direct indexing, as of now. The innovation of direct indexing by automated investment management services has emerged in the U.S since 2015. We are positive about this. Using this method, QuietGrowth can opt for individual stocks instead of ETFs. We at QuietGrowth will not be introducing this at least for sometime.",
			  "url": "faq/Do-you-offer-direct-indexing"
		  , "section": "Your Investment Plan" },
		  {
	  "questionkey": "Where is my money held",
	  "answerkey": "Our partner Saxo Capital Markets SCM holds the Client money in a pooled segregated Client trust account operated by HSBC Bank Australia Segregated Client Account. The Segregated Client Account is kept separate from SCM own money and assets Although Client money is pooled together in the Segregated Client Account SCM will not use money deposited by and belonging to one Client to meet the loss of another Client Moreover SCM does not use Clients money in the Segregated Client Account for its own purposes To ensure SCM complies with the Australian Client Money Rules SCM calculates the value of Clients funds in the Segregated Client Account on a daily basis and reconciles this with the funds available in the Segregated Client Account",
	  "question": "Where is my money held?",
			  "answer": "Our partner Saxo Capital Markets (SCM) holds the Client money in a pooled ‘segregated’ Client trust account operated by HSBC Bank Australia (Segregated Client Account). The Segregated Client Account is kept separate from SCM’s own money and assets.\n\nAlthough Client money is pooled together in the Segregated Client Account, SCM will not use money deposited by (and belonging to) one Client to meet the loss of another Client. Moreover, SCM does not use Clients’ money in the Segregated Client Account for its own purposes.\n\nTo ensure SCM complies with the Australian Client Money Rules, SCM calculates the value of Clients’ funds in the Segregated Client Account on a daily basis and reconciles this with the funds available in the Segregated Client Account.",
			  "url": "faq/Where-is-my-money-held"
		  , "section": "Your account" },
		  {
	  "questionkey": "Where are my securities held",
	  "answerkey": "Our partner Saxo Capital Markets SCM has appointed Saxo Bank as the principal custodian to hold securities on behalf of SCM in an omnibus account which is designated as a client trust account",
	  "question": "Where are my securities held?",
			  "answer": "Our partner Saxo Capital Markets (SCM) has appointed Saxo Bank as the principal custodian to hold securities on behalf of SCM in an omnibus account, which is designated as a client trust account.",
			  "url": "faq/Where-are-my-securities-held"
		  , "section": "Your account" },
		  {
	  "questionkey": "Can I open multiple accounts with QuietGrowth",
	  "answerkey": "You can open as many accounts as you would like to as long as you deposit a minimum initial amount of 2000 in each account",
	  "question": "Can I open multiple accounts with QuietGrowth?",
			  "answer": "You can open as many accounts as you would like to, as long as you deposit a minimum initial amount of $2,000 in each account.",
			  "url": "faq/Can-I-open-multiple-accounts-with-QuietGrowth"
		  , "section": "Creating an account" },
		  {
	  "questionkey": "Why has my online ID verification failed",
	  "answerkey": "We do not know the exact reason for the failure of the electronic verification of your identity We use the services of a third party verification provider who is one of the biggest in the industry A certain percentage of electronic ID verification queries that we conduct fail This happens even though the client provides valid data as per the Government issued documents such as her Drivers Licence In such an instance we ask the client for a certified copy of her identity document For details on the nature of the identity document that we request please refer our Certifying the Identification Document webpage",
	  "question": "Why has my online ID verification failed?",
			  "answer": "We do not know the exact reason for the failure of the electronic verification of your identity. We use the services of a third-party verification provider who is one of the biggest in the industry. A certain percentage of electronic ID verification queries, that we conduct, fail. This happens even though the client provides valid data, as per the Government-issued documents such as her Drivers Licence. In such an instance, we ask the client for a certified copy of her identity document.\n\nFor details on the nature of the identity document that we request, please refer our Certifying the Identification Document webpage.",
			  "url": "faq/Why-has-my-online-ID-verification-failed"
		  , "section": "Creating an account" },
		  {
	  "questionkey": "How can I certify a copy of my identification document",
	  "answerkey": "You can certify a copy of your identification document by following the instructions in the Certifying the Identification Document webpage",
	  "question": "How can I certify a copy of my identification document?",
			  "answer": "You can certify a copy of your identification document by following the instructions in the Certifying the Identification Document webpage.",
			  "url": "faq/How-can-I-certify-a-copy-of-my-identification-document"
		  , "section": "Creating an account" },
		  {
	  "questionkey": "Do you conduct online ID verification of all clients",
	  "answerkey": "We conduct online ID verification of all clients who mention that their current residential address is in Australia For a client who mentions that her current residential address is outside Australia we request her to provide us a certified copy of her ID document For details on the nature of the identity document that we request please refer our Certifying the Identification Document webpage",
	  "question": "Do you conduct online ID verification of all clients?",
			  "answer": "We conduct online ID verification of all clients who mention that their current residential address is in Australia.\n\nFor a client who mentions that her current residential address is outside Australia, we request her to provide us a certified copy of her ID document. For details on the nature of the identity document that we request, please refer our Certifying the Identification Document webpage.",
			  "url": "faq/Do-you-conduct-online-ID-verification-of-all-clients"
		  , "section": "Creating an account" },
		  {
	  "questionkey": "Is it mandatory to submit the W 8BEN or W 8BEN E form",
	  "answerkey": "W BEN form W 8BEN form is used for the following account types Individual Joint Both the individuals who are part of the Joint account type need to submit their individual W 8BEN forms For Individual and Joint account types it is not mandatory to submit a W 8BEN form at the time of account creation with the brokerage firm However we suggest you to provide this form to us at the time of account creation or at a later date the sooner the better You can email us this form at any time even after the creation of your account W 8BEN E form W 8BEN E form is used for the following account types SMSF individual trustee SMSF corporate trustee Trust Company FATCA rules require us to provide to our brokerage firm with certification from Trust and Corporate Company accounts accounts as these are included in the Entities defined under the Intergovernmental Agreement IGA between US and Australia So for Trust and Company account types it is mandatory to submit a W 8BEN E form at the time of account creation with the brokerage firm This helps the brokerage firm to determine the non US or US status of the beneficial owners for tax purposes",
	  "question": "Is it mandatory to submit the W-8BEN or W-8BEN-E form?",
			  "answer": "W-BEN form:\n\nW-8BEN form is used for the following account types:\n\n•   Individual\n\n•   Joint\n\nBoth the individuals who are part of the Joint account type need to submit their individual W-8BEN forms.\n\nFor Individual and Joint account types, it is not mandatory to submit a W-8BEN form at the time of account creation with the brokerage firm. However, we suggest you to provide this form to us, at the time of account creation or at a later date — the sooner the better. You can email us this form at any time, even after the creation of your account.\n\nW-8BEN-E form:\n\nW-8BEN-E form is used for the following account types:\n\n•   SMSF (individual trustee)\n\n•   SMSF (corporate trustee)\n\n•   Trust\n\n•   Company\n\nFATCA rules require us to provide to our brokerage firm with certification from Trust and Corporate/Company accounts accounts, as these are included in the Entities defined under the Intergovernmental Agreement (IGA) between US and Australia.\n\nSo, for Trust and Company account types, it is mandatory to submit a W-8BEN-E form at the time of account creation with the brokerage firm. This helps the brokerage firm to determine the non-US or US status of the beneficial owners for tax purposes.",
			  "url": "faq/Is-it-mandatory-to-submit-the-W-8BEN-or-W-8BEN-E-form"
		  , "section": "Creating an account" },
		  {
	  "questionkey": "What is the relevance of W 8BEN or W 8BEN E forms",
	  "answerkey": "All US dividends from investment in any US securities that are part of a QuietGrowth Portfolio are subject to a 30 withholding tax enforced by the Internal Revenue Service IRS For QuietGrowth clients our brokerage partner can offer US relief at source reducing the overall withholding tax on dividends from 30 to 15 by applying the double taxation treaty between Australia and United States of America US tax relief at source reduces the overall withholding tax on dividends from 30 to 15 In order to benefit from the US tax relief at source QuietGrowth clients are required to complete the relevant W 8BEN or W 8BEN E form Please note that QuietGrowth does not provide any advice on tax related services The Internal Revenue Service IRS is a US government agency responsible for tax collection and tax law enforcement If you have queries while filling the W 8BEN or W 8BEN E form you would need to refer to the relevant instructions available in the IRS website or obtain advice from your tax expert",
	  "question": "What is the relevance of W-8BEN or W-8BEN-E forms?",
			  "answer": "All US dividends from investment in any US securities, that are part of a QuietGrowth Portfolio, are subject to a 30% withholding tax enforced by the Internal Revenue Service (IRS). For QuietGrowth clients, our brokerage partner can offer US relief at source reducing the overall withholding tax on dividends from 30% to 15% by applying the double taxation treaty between Australia and United States of America. US tax relief at source reduces the overall withholding tax on dividends from 30% to 15%. In order to benefit from the US tax relief at source, QuietGrowth clients are required to complete the relevant W-8BEN or W-8BEN-E form.\n\nPlease note that QuietGrowth does not provide any advice on tax related services. The Internal Revenue Service (IRS) is a US government agency responsible for tax collection and tax law enforcement. If you have queries while filling the W-8BEN or W-8BEN-E form, you would need to refer to the relevant instructions available in the IRS website, or obtain advice from your tax expert.",
			  "url": "faq/What-is-the-relevance-of-W-8BEN-or-W-8BEN-E-forms"
		  , "section": "Creating an account" },
		  {
	  "questionkey": "Do I need to certify all the pages of my Trust deed",
	  "answerkey": "It is sufficient if you certify the following pages in the trust deed The cover page bearing the name of the Trust The schedule page having the names of the trustees the names of the beneficiaries and date of registration of the Trust The signature/execution page For details on how to certify the document refer Certifying the Document webpage",
	  "question": "Do I need to certify all the pages of my Trust deed?",
			  "answer": "It is sufficient if you certify the following pages in the trust deed:\n\nThe cover page bearing the name of the Trust\nThe schedule page having the names of the trustees, the names of the beneficiaries and date of registration of the Trust.\nThe signature/execution page\nFor details on how to certify the document, refer Certifying the Document webpage.",
			  "url": "faq/Do-I-need-to-certify-all-the-pages-of-my-Trust-deed"
		  , "section": "Creating an account — SMSF and Trust account types" },
		  {
	  "questionkey": "Can US residents open an account with QuietGrowth",
	  "answerkey": "No US residents or entities of the United States of America cannot open an account with QuietGrowth because we will be not be able to create a brokerage account for such clients through our brokerage partner At the time of account creation we take a confirmation from anyone who is currently living in the US whether she is a US resident and she has been staying in the US for more than six months",
	  "question": "Can US residents open an account with QuietGrowth?",
			  "answer": "No, US residents or entities of the United States of America cannot open an account with QuietGrowth, because we will be not be able to create a brokerage account for such clients through our brokerage partner. At the time of account creation, we take a confirmation from anyone who is currently living in the US whether she is a US resident and she has been staying in the US for more than six months.",
			  "url": "faq/Can-US-residents-open-an-account-with-QuietGrowth"
		  , "section": "Creating an account — Residents of other countries" },
		  {
	  "questionkey": "Can I make monthly contributions to QuietGrowth",
	  "answerkey": "Yes you can make monthly contributions after setting up an account with QuietGrowth with the minimum investment of $2000 The contributions can be daily weekly monthly or in any other frequency You can give instructions to your bank to set up an automatic direct deposit from your bank account to your brokerage account created by QuietGrowth Or you can manually transfer money from your bank account whenever you want",
	  "question": "Can I make monthly contributions to QuietGrowth?",
			  "answer": "Yes, you can make monthly contributions, after setting up an account with QuietGrowth with the minimum investment of $2,000. The contributions can be daily, weekly, monthly or in any other frequency.\n\nYou can give instructions to your bank to set up an automatic direct deposit from your bank account to your brokerage account created by QuietGrowth. Or, you can manually transfer money from your bank account whenever you want.",
			  "url": "faq/Can-I-make-monthly-contributions-to-QuietGrowth"
		  , "section": "Adding funds" },
		  {
	  "questionkey": "Can I invest in multiple portfolios",
	  "answerkey": "Yes you can invest in more than one portfolio with each having a different portfolio risk Multiple risk portfolios enable you to have a goal based investment program with the flexibility to tailor your investment portfolio towards particular needs The minimum initial investment in each of the newly created portfolios is $2 000",
	  "question": "Can I invest in multiple portfolios?",
			  "answer": "Yes, you can invest in more than one portfolio, with each having a different portfolio risk. Multiple risk portfolios enable you to have a goal-based investment program with the flexibility to tailor your investment portfolio towards particular needs. The minimum initial investment in each of the newly created portfolios is $2,000.",
			  "url": "faq/Can-I-invest-in-multiple-portfolios"
		  , "section": "Multiple portfolios" },
		  {
	  "questionkey": "Do you provide goals-based investing",
	  "answerkey": "Yes you can set up multiple risk portfolios for different investing goals that you might have Depending on the nature of your investing goal you can specify the risk tolerance for each of these portfolios",
	  "question": "Do you provide goals-based investing?",
			  "answer": "Yes, you can set up multiple risk portfolios for different investing goals that you might have. Depending on the nature of your investing goal, you can specify the risk tolerance for each of these portfolios.",
			  "url": "faq/Do-you-provide-goals-based-investing"
		  , "section": "Multiple portfolios" },
		  {
	  "questionkey": "Can I change the risk tolerance of a portfolio",
	  "answerkey": "Yes you can alter the risk tolerance of a portfolio as long as as the new risk tolerance of that portfolio is lesser than or equal to the risk tolerance that is advised by QuietGrowth to you The highest risk category that any of the portfolios of a client can have is the advised risk tolerance score You can alter the risk tolerance of a portfolio at most once a month",
	  "question": "Can I change the risk tolerance of a portfolio?",
			  "answer": "Yes, you can alter the risk tolerance of a portfolio, as long as as the new risk tolerance of that portfolio is lesser than or equal to the risk tolerance that is advised by QuietGrowth to you. The highest risk category that any of the portfolios of a client can have is the 'advised risk tolerance score'.\n\nYou can alter the risk tolerance of a portfolio at most once a month.",
			  "url": "faq/Can-I-change-the-risk-tolerance-of-a-portfolio"
		  , "section": "Multiple portfolios" },
		  {
	  "questionkey": "Can I merge one portfolio into another portfolio",
	  "answerkey": "Yes you can merge one portfolio into another portfolio We will move your holdings from the portfolio that you do not want to the destination portfolio The risk tolerance score of the destination portfolio will be continued No buy or sell trades will be executed for the holdings in your portfolio that you do not want Hence you will not be subjected to any realised capital gains or losses from this",
	  "question": "Can I merge one portfolio into another portfolio?",
			  "answer": "Yes, you can merge one portfolio into another portfolio. We will move your holdings from the portfolio that you do not want, to the destination portfolio. The risk tolerance score of the destination portfolio will be continued.\n\nNo buy or sell trades will be executed for the holdings in your portfolio that you do not want. Hence you will not be subjected to any realised capital gains or losses from this.",
			  "url": "faq/Can-I-merge-one-portfolio-into-another-portfolio"
		  , "section": "Multiple portfolios" },
		  {
	  "questionkey": "Can I invest for my kids through QuietGrowth",
	  "answerkey": "Yes you can invest for your kids with QuietGrowth However your kids cannot invest by themselves through QuietGrowth This is because an individual has to be at least 18 years old to open a QuietGrowth account Below are three options for you to invest for your child or grandchild with QuietGrowth Option New QuietGrowth account is opened Legal owner Add a new portfolio in your existing QuietGrowth account keeping in mind that the portfolio in your account is meant for your kids You can name the new portfolio as Kids or something similar for your reference No You continue to be the legal owner of all the portfolios in your existing QuietGrowth account Open a separate QuietGrowth account with Individual account type and invest in that account keeping in mind that all the portfolios in that account is meant for your kids Yes You become the legal owner of the new QuietGrowth account Set up a Family Trust or Discretionary Trust add yourself as a trustee and add your kids as beneficiaries Then the trustee of that trust opens a QuietGrowth account with the Trust account type Yes The trust becomes the legal owner of the new QuietGrowth account For any tax implications resulting from setting up a trust we recommend you to speak with your tax adviser For setting up a family trust please contact your accountant or lawyer or someone authorised to set up a trust We at QuietGrowth do not set up a trust",
	  "question": "Can I invest for my kids through QuietGrowth?",
			  "answer": "Yes, you can invest for your kids with QuietGrowth. However, your kids cannot invest by themselves through QuietGrowth. This is because an individual has to be at least 18 years old to open a QuietGrowth account.\n\nBelow are three options for you to invest for your child or grandchild with QuietGrowth.\n\nOption New QuietGrowth account is opened? Legal owner\n1 Add a new portfolio in your existing QuietGrowth account, keeping in mind that the portfolio in your account is meant for your kids. You can name the new portfolio as 'Kids' or something similar for your reference. No You continue to be the legal owner of all the portfolios in your existing QuietGrowth account.\n2 Open a separate QuietGrowth account with ‘Individual’ account type and invest in that account keeping in mind that all the portfolios in that account is meant for your kids. Yes You become the legal owner of the new QuietGrowth account.\n3 Set up a Family Trust or Discretionary Trust, add yourself as a trustee and add your kids as beneficiaries. Then the trustee of that trust opens a QuietGrowth account with the 'Trust' account type. Yes The trust becomes the legal owner of the new QuietGrowth account.\nFor any tax implications resulting from setting up a trust, we recommend you to speak with your tax adviser.\n\nFor setting up a family trust, please contact your accountant or lawyer or someone authorised to set up a trust. We at QuietGrowth do not set up a trust.",
			  "url": "faq/Can-I-invest-for-my-kids-through-QuietGrowth"
		  , "section": "QuietGrowth Kids" },
		  {
	  "questionkey": "How much can I withdraw",
	  "answerkey": "You can withdraw a minimum of $5000 as often as you would like as long as you maintain a minimum balance of $2000 in your QuietGrowth account If your portfolio value is less than $7000 then you would need to close your portfolio and withdraw the entire amount",
	  "question": "How much can I withdraw?",
			  "answer": "You can withdraw a minimum of $5,000 as often as you would like, as long as you maintain a minimum balance of $2,000 in your QuietGrowth account.\n\nIf your portfolio value is less than $7,000, then you would need to close your portfolio and withdraw the entire amount.",
			  "url": "faq/How-much-can-I-withdraw"
		  , "section": "Withdrawals" },
		  {
	  "questionkey": "Is there a lock in period",
	  "answerkey": "There is no minimum period or lock-in. You have the option to withdraw your money at any time However you may need to contact your tax consultant to consider the impact of capital gains tax at the time of withdrawal",
	  "question": "Is there a lock in period?",
			  "answer": "There is no minimum period or lock-in. You have the option to withdraw your money at any time.\n\nHowever, you may need to contact your tax consultant to consider the impact of capital gains tax at the time of withdrawal.",
			  "url": "faq/Is-there-a-lock-in-period"
		  , "section": "Withdrawals" },
		  {
	  "questionkey": "What is the withdrawal process",
	  "answerkey": "You can place a withdrawal request in QuietGrowth website whenever you intend to withdraw your money After you confirm your withdrawal request you would need to provide the signed withdrawal form For your first withdrawal you would also need to provide the details of your bank account To ensure that the bank account details mentioned by you actually belongs to you we need a photo or screenshot of portion of your bank statement or portion of the online bank webpage that contains the following information The name of the bank Your name in the bank account Bank account number BSB number preferable to have this too There is no need to provide this document for your subsequent withdrawals Note that if a document containing your signature is not in our records then we might also ask for a document containing your signature so that we can match your signature in your signed withdrawal form with the signature in that document Then within a reasonable period we will execute the necessary sell trades in your brokerage account so that the money generated by divesting your holdings is credited to your brokerage account After that it usually takes about 2 to 5 business days for the money to reach your bank account from your brokerage account",
	  "question": "What is the withdrawal process?",
			  "answer": "You can place a withdrawal request in QuietGrowth website, whenever you intend to withdraw your money.\n\nAfter you confirm your withdrawal request, you would need to provide the signed withdrawal form.\n\nFor your first withdrawal, you would also need to provide the details of your bank account. To ensure that the bank account details mentioned by you actually belongs to you, we need a photo or screenshot of portion of your bank statement or portion of the online bank webpage that contains the following information:\n\na) The name of the bank\n\nb) Your name in the bank account\n\nc) Bank account number\n\nd) BSB number (preferable to have this too)\n\nThere is no need to provide this document for your subsequent withdrawals.\n\n(Note that if a document containing your signature is not in our records, then we might also ask for a document containing your signature, so that we can match your signature in your signed withdrawal form with the signature in that document.)\n\nThen, within a reasonable period, we will execute the necessary sell trades in your brokerage account, so that the money generated by divesting your holdings is credited to your brokerage account. After that, it usually takes about 2 to 5 business days for the money to reach your bank account from your brokerage account.",
			  "url": "faq/What-is-the-withdrawal-process"
		  , "section": "Withdrawals" },
		  {
	  "questionkey": "Does QuietGrowth provide fingerprint security",
	  "answerkey": "Yes QuietGrowth provides fingerprint security feature for its iOS and Android mobile apps This feature is referred to as Touch ID for the iOS mobile app",
	  "question": "Does QuietGrowth provide fingerprint security?",
			  "answer": "Yes, QuietGrowth provides fingerprint security feature for its iOS and Android mobile apps. This feature is referred to as Touch ID for the iOS mobile app.",
			  "url": "faq/Does-QuietGrowth-provide-fingerprint-security"
		  , "section": "Security" },
		  {
	  "questionkey": "Does QuietGrowth provide two factor authentication",
	  "answerkey": "Yes QuietGrowth provides two factor authentication security feature for the website as well as for the mobile apps iOS and Android",
	  "question": "Does QuietGrowth provide two-factor authentication?",
			  "answer": "Yes, QuietGrowth provides two-factor authentication security feature for the website, as well as for the mobile apps (iOS and Android).",
			  "url": "faq/Does-QuietGrowth-provide-two-factor-authentication"
		  , "section": "Security" },
		  {
	  "questionkey": "Where are the servers located",
	  "answerkey": "Our servers are located in Australia",
	  "question": "Where are the servers located?",
			  "answer": "Our servers are located in Australia.",
			  "url": "faq/Where-are-the-servers-located"
		  , "section": "Security" },
		  {
	  "questionkey": "Do you provide financial advice or investment advice",
	  "answerkey": "We provide both financial advice and investment advice Investment advice generally means personal financial advice about investment topics As we provide you the QuietGrowth service through the Managed Discretionary Account MDA structure our personal financial advice is limited to the suitability of the client to the MDA service of QuietGrowth",
	  "question": "Do you provide financial advice or investment advice?",
			  "answer": "We provide both financial advice and investment advice. Investment advice generally means personal financial advice about investment topics.\n\nAs we provide you the QuietGrowth service through the Managed Discretionary Account (MDA) structure, our personal financial advice is limited to the suitability of the client to the MDA service of QuietGrowth.",
			  "url": "faq/Do-you-provide-financial-advice-or-investment-advice"
		  , "section": "Structure of QuietGrowth service" },
		  {
	  "questionkey": "What is the purpose of Statement of Advice",
	  "answerkey": "A Statement of Advice SOA is a document that sets out your situation and goals and our corresponding financial advice You will receive an SOA when we provide you with personal financial advice that takes into consideration your personal objectives financial situation and needs The SOA will contain the advice the basis on which it was given information about fees commissions and associations related to the provision of this advice Read our Financial Services Guide to know more",
	  "question": "What is the purpose of Statement of Advice?",
			  "answer": "A Statement of Advice (SOA) is a document that sets out your situation and goals, and our corresponding financial advice. You will receive an SOA when we provide you with personal financial advice that takes into consideration your personal objectives, financial situation and needs. The SOA will contain:\n\n•  the advice\n\n•  the basis on which it was given\n\n•  information about fees, commissions and associations related to the provision of this advice.\n\nRead our Financial Services Guide to know more.",
			  "url": "faq/What-is-the-purpose-of-Statement-of-Advice"
		  , "section": "Structure of QuietGrowth service" },
		  {
	  "questionkey": "Is QuietGrowth a financial adviser",
	  "answerkey": "Yes QuietGrowth is a financial adviser We provide personal financial advice Our service is also referred to as robo advice or digital advice",
	  "question": "Is QuietGrowth a financial adviser?",
			  "answer": "Yes, QuietGrowth is a financial adviser. We provide personal financial advice. Our service is also referred to as robo advice or digital advice.",
			  "url": "faq/Is-QuietGrowth-a-financial-adviser"
		  , "section": "Structure of QuietGrowth service" },
		  {
	  "questionkey": "Is there a HIN for my investments in securities",
	  "answerkey": "The ETF investments in your QuietGrowth portfolio are not structured as the Holder Identification Number HIN model A brokerage account is created in your own name And your deposits are transferred directly from your bank account to your brokerage account Also read our answer to the following questions  Where are my securities held Where is my money held",
	  "question": "Is there a HIN for my investments in securities?",
			  "answer": "The ETF investments in your QuietGrowth portfolio are not structured as the Holder Identification Number (HIN) model.\n\nA brokerage account is created in your own name. And your deposits are transferred directly from your bank account to your brokerage account.\n\nAlso, read our answer to the following questions:\n\n•  Where are my securities held?\n\n•  Where is my money held?",
			  "url": "faq/Is-there-a-HIN-for-my-investments-in-securities"
		  , "section": "Structure of QuietGrowth service" },
		  {
	  "questionkey": "Do you earn commissions from product issuers",
	  "answerkey": "QuietGrowth is independent from all the ETF product issuers whose products we include in our portfolios because of the following reasons We do not earn commissions or remuneration from ETF product issuers We do not receive gifts or benefits from product issuers which may reasonably be expected to influence us None of the product issuing firms are shareholders in our company Because of these practices conflicted remuneration does not exist between QuietGrowth and ETF product issuers",
	  "question": "Do you earn commissions from product issuers?",
			  "answer": "QuietGrowth is independent from all the ETF product issuers, whose products we include in our portfolios, because of the following reasons:\n\nWe do not earn commissions or remuneration from ETF product issuers.\nWe do not receive gifts or benefits from product issuers which may reasonably be expected to influence us.\nNone of the product issuing firms are shareholders in our company.\nBecause of these practices, conflicted remuneration does not exist between QuietGrowth and ETF product issuers.",
			  "url": "faq/Do-you-earn-commissions-from-product-issuers"
		  , "section": "Structure of QuietGrowth service" },
		  {
	  "questionkey": "Do I need to inform QuietGrowth before I add funds or can I directly transfer the amount without informing",
	  "answerkey": "We suggest that you login to your QuietGrowth account and notify us about your inclination to deposit an amount to your brokerage account You informing us before the transfer will help us to anticipate your transferring of the amount However it is not mandatory for you to log in to your QuietGrowth account and notify us about your inclination to deposit an amount to your brokerage account You may deposit the amount to your brokerage account from your bank account without informing QuietGrowth At the time of transferring the deposit from your bank account to your brokerage account you would need to mention in the reference field your account reference details that you can access in the QuietGrowth website When that amount from your bank account is transferred successfully to your brokerage account we would be able to see that bank transaction in your brokerage account We will book that amount to your brokerage account and we will start managing the money for you as soon as the deposit is made available in your brokerage account",
	  "question": "Do I need to inform QuietGrowth before I add funds, or can I directly transfer the amount without informing?",
	  "answer": "We suggest that you login to your QuietGrowth account and notify us about your inclination to deposit an amount to your brokerage account. You informing us before the transfer will help us to anticipate your transferring of the amount.\n\nHowever, it is not mandatory for you to log in to your QuietGrowth account and notify us about your inclination to deposit an amount to your brokerage account. You may deposit the amount to your brokerage account from your bank account without informing QuietGrowth. At the time of transferring the deposit from your bank account to your brokerage account, you would need to mention in the reference field your account reference details that you can access in the QuietGrowth website. When that amount from your bank account is transferred successfully to your brokerage account, we would be able to see that bank transaction in your brokerage account. We will book that amount to your brokerage account, and we will start managing the money for you as soon as the deposit is made available in your brokerage account.",
	  "url": "faq/Do-I-need-to-inform-QuietGrowth-before-I-add-funds-or-can-I-directly-transfer-the-amount-without-informing"
	, "section": "Adding funds" },
	{
	  "questionkey": "What will stop me from investing $50000 with you and then replicate the trades for my remaining $250000 portfolio at a discount broker",
	  "answerkey": "Nothing However do you not realise that it is extra work for you through the period of the investment and sometimes more expensive for you Especially when we only charge you an annual QuietGrowth fee as low as 0.4 per annum moreover the first $10000 in assets is managed free of QuietGrowth fee to execute all the trades in your account to perform the activity of rebalancing and to offer our service with zero brokerage trading charges",
	  "question": "What will stop me from investing $50,000 with you, and then replicate the trades for my remaining $250,000 portfolio at a discount broker?",
	  "answer": "Nothing. However, do you not realise that it is extra work for you through the period of the investment, and sometimes more expensive for you? Especially when we only charge you an annual QuietGrowth fee as low as 0.4% per annum (moreover, the first $10,000 in assets is managed free of QuietGrowth fee) to execute all the trades in your account, to perform the activity of rebalancing and to offer our service with zero brokerage/trading charges.",
	  "url": "faq/What-will-stop-me-from-investing-50000-with-you-and-then-replicate-the-trades-for-my-remaining-250000-portfolio-at-a-discount-broker"
		  , "section": "Fees" },
		  {
			  "questionkey": "What to do if the character limit of the reference message allowed by my bank is too low",
			  "answerkey": "At the time of transferring the deposit from your bank account to your brokerage account linked to your QuietGrowth account you would need to provide a reference message in the reference field The reference message will be in the format “XXXXXXX AAA BBB CCC” where XXXXXXX is a unique number provided to you, AAA is your first name, BBB is your middle name and CCC is your last name. You can access your reference message by logging in to your QuietGrowth account However many banks have a low limit to the character count in the message section of the bank transfer In such a situation if you mention at least the unique number which is present at the starting of the reference message in the format XXXXXXX in the message section of the bank transfer your deposit will take place and the amount will be booked into your brokerage account by the brokerage firm",
			  "question": "What to do if the character limit of the reference message allowed by my bank is too low?",
			  "answer": "At the time of transferring the deposit from your bank account to your brokerage account linked to your QuietGrowth account, you would need to provide a reference message in the reference field. The reference message will be in the format “XXXXXXX AAA BBB CCC” where XXXXXXX is a unique number provided to you, AAA is your first name, BBB is your middle name and CCC is your last name. You can access your reference message by logging in to your QuietGrowth account.\n\nHowever, many banks have a low limit to the character count in the message section of the bank transfer. In such a situation, if you mention at least the unique number (which is present at the starting of the reference message in the format XXXXXXX) in the message section of the bank transfer, your deposit will take place, and the amount will be booked into your brokerage account by the brokerage firm.",
			  "url": "faq/What-to-do-if-the-character-limit-of-the-reference-message-allowed-by-my-bank-is-too-low", 
		  "section": "Adding funds" 
		  },
		  {
			  "questionkey": "What do you mean by a fully  diversified portfolio",
			  "answerkey": "A QuietGrowth Portfolio comprises of a certain number of ETFs If the deposited money in your QuietGrowth Portfolio is invested in all these ETFs then we refer to that portfolio of yours as a fully diversified portfolio",
			  "question": "What do you mean by a 'fully-diversified portfolio'?",
			  "answer": "A QuietGrowth Portfolio comprises of a certain number of ETFs. If the deposited money in your QuietGrowth Portfolio is invested in all these ETFs, then we refer to that portfolio of yours as a 'fully-diversified portfolio'.",
			  "url": "faq/What-do-you-mean-by-a-fully-diversified-portfolio", 
		  "section": "Adding funds" 

		  },
		  {
			  "questionkey": "If I close my account before the end of the financial year will I still get documents for tax filing",
			  "answerkey": "Yes. Even if you close your QuietGrowth account before the end of the financial year you will still get documents from QuietGrowth that you can use to file your tax returns You will get these documents after the end of that financial year even though you would not be a QuietGrowth client at that point of time.",
			  "question": "If I close my account before the end of the financial year, will I still get documents for tax filing?",
			  "answer": "Yes. Even if you close your QuietGrowth account before the end of the financial year, you will still get documents from QuietGrowth that you can use to file your tax returns. You will get these documents after the end of that financial year, even though you would not be a QuietGrowth client at that point of time.",
			  "url": "faq/If-I-close-my-account-before-the-end-of-the-financial-year-will-I-still-get-documents-tax-filing", 
		  "section": "Taxes" 

		  }
	  ]
